<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Yihong Liu&#39;s Blog</title>
        <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com</link>
        <description>Yihong Liu is a PhD student in the Management Science, Information Systems Concentration at the Naveen Jindal School of Management, UT Dallas.</description>
        <language>en</language>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:42:12 -0500</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:42:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <category>JSOM</category>
        <category>Ph.D.</category>
        <category>Notes</category>
        <category>SQL</category>
        <category>ITSS3300</category>
        <category>Writing</category>
        <category>Latex</category>
        <category>Packages</category>
        <category>PGF/TikZ</category>
        <category>Job</category>
        <category>Interview Experiences</category>
        <category>Research</category>
        <category>MIS</category>
        <category>IS</category>
        <category>Management Information Systems</category>
        <category>Information Systems</category>
        <category>Conference</category>
        <category>Calendar</category>
        <category>Math</category>
        <category>Preliminary</category>
        <category>Courses</category>
        <category>Online Video Community</category>
        <category>Bilibili</category>
        <category>Business Model</category>
        <category>Video Collaboration</category>
        <category>哔哩哔哩</category>
        <category>B站</category>
        <category>商业模型</category>
        <category>联合投稿</category>
        <category>Personalized Ranking</category>
        <category>Implicit Feedback</category>
        <category>Reading</category>
        <category>Publications</category>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/</guid>
            <title>Crack the Academic Job Hunt Code: Insider Tips</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/</link>
            <category>Ph.D.</category>
            <category>Notes</category>
            <category>Job</category>
            <category>Interview Experiences</category>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 00:42:12 -0500</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;Are you lost in the maze of academia’s job hunt? Discover the insider tips and wisdom from seasoned professors who’ve been on both sides of the hiring table. From crafting the perfect CV to avoiding common pitfalls, our panelists spill the beans on positioning yourself as a standout candidate. Get ready to demystify the opaque world of academic recruiting and supercharge your odds of success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Job hunting in academia can feel like navigating a maze blindfolded. From tailoring application materials to acing interviews, the process requires skill, strategy, and a bit of luck. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s why my notes from the &lt;strong&gt;INFORMS 2023 Minority Issue Forum&lt;/strong&gt; on the academic job search offer a glimpse behind the curtain. On October 18th, seasoned professors peeled back the veil, sharing their experiences and insights from both sides of the hiring table. Their advice, captured here, sheds light on practices for positioning yourself as an outstanding candidate. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From building your CV to avoiding common pitfalls, these tips aim to demystify the opaque world of academic recruiting. With wisdom across fields like engineering and business, my notes provide a look at landing your dream academic job. Though the hunt itself may still prove challenging, arming yourself with this insider knowledge can only help your odds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;article class=&#34;message is-warning is-default&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;message-header&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-exclamation-triangle mr-2&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;This note is a combination of panelists’ talks and my personal interpretation. It reflects not only panelists’ wisdom and my personal bias. It is generally applicable, but may not be always true.&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/article&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would like to extend my gratitude to the four panelists who generously shared their insights into the academic job search process. Our panelists, Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://home.csulb.edu/~bbehzad/home.html&#34;&gt;Banafsheh Behzad&lt;/a&gt;, Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://directory.smeal.psu.edu/jpa5602&#34;&gt;Johanna Amaya&lt;/a&gt;, Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.umass.edu/engineering/about/directory/muge-capan&#34;&gt;Muge Capan&lt;/a&gt;, and Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://engineering.buffalo.edu/industrial-systems/people/faculty-directory.host.html/content/shared/engineering/industrial-systems/profiles/faculty/dell-robert.html&#34;&gt;Robert Dell&lt;/a&gt;, brought diverse experiences to the discussion. I’d also like to acknowledge the efforts of our session chairs, Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://faculty.txst.edu/profile/1922475&#34;&gt;Clara M. Novoa Ramirez&lt;/a&gt; and Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://engineering.buffalo.edu/industrial-systems/people/faculty-directory.host.html/content/shared/engineering/industrial-systems/profiles/faculty/ramirez-rios-diana.html&#34;&gt;Diana Ramirez-Rios&lt;/a&gt;, for organizing this informative session.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Question-1-What-Is-Your-Experience-in-the-Academic-Job-Search-Process&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Question-1-What-Is-Your-Experience-in-the-Academic-Job-Search-Process&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Question 1 : What Is Your Experience in the Academic Job Search Process?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Question 1 : What Is Your Experience in the Academic Job Search Process?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our panelists bring a wealth of diverse experiences to the table in the academic job search process. Each of them has held distinct roles in this journey, contributing to a well-rounded perspective:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leadership Roles&lt;/strong&gt; : Some of our panelists have served as deans or provosts of graduate schools, offering insights into the administrative aspects of academic recruitment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Search Committee Expertise&lt;/strong&gt; : Others have been actively involved in search committees, making critical decisions about candidate selection and hiring.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transition between Research and Teaching&lt;/strong&gt; : A few of our panelists began their careers as scientists before transitioning into academia as teaching faculty members, ultimately embarking on the tenure track as assistant professors with a strong focus on research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Balancing Teaching and Research&lt;/strong&gt; : Additionally, our panelists have experience in both teaching and research positions, giving them a comprehensive view of the expectations and challenges in these roles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This collective expertise ensures that the advice shared during this forum covers a broad spectrum of experiences and positions, making it applicable to a wide range of individuals aspiring to secure their dream academic job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Question-2-What-Is-the-First-Document-You-Look-at-When-Reviewing-an-Applicant’s-Package&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Question-2-What-Is-the-First-Document-You-Look-at-When-Reviewing-an-Applicant’s-Package&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Question 2: What Is the First Document You Look at When Reviewing an Applicant’s Package?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Question 2: What Is the First Document You Look at When Reviewing an Applicant’s Package?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our panelists shared insights on what catches their attention first when reviewing academic job applications. It’s worth noting that different panelists had varying approaches, but the consensus was clear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The CV&amp;#x2F;Resume&lt;/strong&gt; : Many panelists begin by examining the applicant’s CV or resume. This is often the starting point because it provides a snapshot of your academic journey. What are they looking for in your CV?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research Topics and Collaborations&lt;/strong&gt; : They pay close attention to the research topics you’ve committed to and the co-authors you’ve worked with. This gives them insight into your research interests, your fit with the position’s requirements, and your professional connections.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Sequence Matters&lt;/strong&gt; : If your CV passes the initial test, the review process usually continues with the cover letter, research statement, and teaching statement. Your CV is like the first impression, and the other documents provide a more in-depth understanding of your qualifications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personalization is Key&lt;/strong&gt; : Our panelists stressed the importance of personalization throughout your application. They want to know why you’re interested in their school, what specific topics you plan to work on if hired, and who you see yourself collaborating with on those identified topics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion (DEI) Statement&lt;/strong&gt;: If the job posting requires a DEI statement, our panelists emphasized the significance of this document. It’s not just about making a general statement on diversity and inclusion, but rather contextualizing your beliefs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defining DEI&lt;/strong&gt; : Explain how you define diversity, equity, and inclusion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personal Connection&lt;/strong&gt; : Share how DEI matters to you and how it shapes your approach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Integration in Teaching and Research&lt;/strong&gt; : Illustrate how DEI principles are woven into your teaching and research.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The panelists were clear that a “desk reject” (rejection without further consideration) could happen if the DEI statement is required but not submitted. So, don’t overlook this aspect if it’s part of the application requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Question-3-What-Is-the-Most-Challenging-Part-of-the-Job-Search-Process&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Question-3-What-Is-the-Most-Challenging-Part-of-the-Job-Search-Process&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Question 3: What Is the Most Challenging Part of the Job Search Process?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Question 3: What Is the Most Challenging Part of the Job Search Process?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keeping Track of Applications:&lt;/strong&gt; Several panelists emphasized the difficulty of staying organized throughout the application process. As the number of applications increases, it can become increasingly challenging to manage all the necessary documents, deadlines, and personalization requirements for each school. This includes tailoring your application materials to match the specific needs and preferences of each institution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Choosing the Right Type of School:&lt;/strong&gt; Another point of discussion revolved around the decision to apply for positions in business schools versus engineering schools. Panelists had differing opinions on this matter. While some believed that there should be no restrictions on the types of schools you consider, it’s crucial to be aware of the differences between these two school types. These distinctions encompass cultural aspects, expectations, deliverables, and tenure criteria. So, when deciding where to apply, it’s vital to consider how well your background and aspirations align with the unique characteristics of the department or school.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategic Application:&lt;/strong&gt; Panelists also emphasized the importance of applying strategically. They advised prospective job seekers to have a clear understanding of their goals, reasons for wanting to join a particular school, and how well they fit within the department’s culture. In other words, it’s not just about the quantity of applications, but also about the quality and alignment of your applications with your career aspirations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Question-4-What-Are-the-Dos-and-Don’ts-in-the-Job-Search-Process&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Question-4-What-Are-the-Dos-and-Don’ts-in-the-Job-Search-Process&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Question 4: What Are the Dos and Don’ts in the Job Search Process?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Question 4: What Are the Dos and Don’ts in the Job Search Process?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dos&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Craft an Engaging Elevator Speech:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your elevator speech should succinctly highlight your research interests, achievements, and future plans. Make it captivating and relevant to your field. This is often your first impression, so it’s crucial to grab the committee’s attention.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Know the Search Committee Members:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do your homework and familiarize yourself with the members of the search committee. Understand their areas of interest and expertise. This will enable you to tailor your conversation to topics of mutual interest and demonstrate how your skills complement the program’s needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’ts&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t Apply Blindly:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid applying to institutions that you are absolutely certain you wouldn’t want to join. Your application should be a reflection of your genuine interest in the position and the institution, not a scattergun approach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t Obsess Over Tenure Criteria:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While tenure is important, don’t let it overwhelm your job search process. Focus on showcasing your qualifications and fit for the position. Tenure discussions can happen later in the process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;3&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t Overdo It in Interviews:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It’s important to be yourself during interviews. Trying too hard to impress can come across as insincere. Let your authentic self shine through, allowing the search committee to make an informed judgment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Don’t Exceed Time Limits:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stick to the allotted time when answering interview questions. Finishing on time shows respect for the committee’s schedule and allows them to ask more questions and learn more about you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;5&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid Lengthy Publication Lists:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When presenting your research profile, avoid overwhelming the committee with a long list of publications. Instead, provide a concise summary of your key takeaways, emphasizing the knowledge, accomplishments, and contributions that are most relevant to the position and the institution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Question-5-Should-Applicants-from-Minority-Represented-Groups-Conceal-Their-Background&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Question-5-Should-Applicants-from-Minority-Represented-Groups-Conceal-Their-Background&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Question 5: Should Applicants from Minority-Represented Groups Conceal Their Background?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Question 5: Should Applicants from Minority-Represented Groups Conceal Their Background?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;All panelists unanimously agree that applicants should approach their minority-represented status with transparency and confidence. It is essential to never hide or downplay one’s belonging to a minority group, whether it’s related to culture, background, or ability. These unique characteristics can offer valuable perspectives and contribute to Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion (DEI) efforts within academia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Applicants are encouraged to take pride in what makes them unique and to share how these distinctive aspects are reflected in their research and teaching. There’s no need to feel shy or ashamed about your background or identity. Embracing your true self is key. Instead of trying to conform to a perceived norm, let the match between you and the institution occur naturally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Question-6-What-Sets-Apart-Virtual-Interviews-from-In-Person-Interviews&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Question-6-What-Sets-Apart-Virtual-Interviews-from-In-Person-Interviews&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Question 6: What Sets Apart Virtual Interviews from In-Person Interviews?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Question 6: What Sets Apart Virtual Interviews from In-Person Interviews?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Virtual Interviews as a Marathon:&lt;/strong&gt; Some of our panelists described virtual interviews, particularly the campus visit ones, as marathon events. This is because in a virtual setting, you don’t have the luxury of time between one-on-one conversations, unlike in-person interviews where you can physically move from one office to another. This tight schedule can make virtual interviews more challenging in terms of time management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Value of In-Person Connection:&lt;/strong&gt; On the other hand, some panelists expressed a preference for in-person interviews due to the physical contact and face-to-face experience they offer. Building a personal connection and rapport with interviewers and the campus community can be easier in an in-person setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Controlling Noise Levels:&lt;/strong&gt; Regardless of whether it’s a virtual or in-person interview, our panelists emphasized the importance of controlling noise levels during the interview. Background noise or disruptions can detract from your presentation and the panel’s ability to focus, so it’s crucial to find a quiet and distraction-free environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adapting to Lecture Modalities:&lt;/strong&gt; Another important point raised by our panelists was the need for candidates to be aware of the various lecture modalities, such as offline, online, and hybrid teaching, and the evolving student population. As academic job seekers, you should be prepared to adjust your teaching methods to accommodate different lecture formats and cater to diverse student learning styles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Audience-Question-1-How-to-Deliver-the-First-Impression-Effectively-in-the-Interview&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Audience-Question-1-How-to-Deliver-the-First-Impression-Effectively-in-the-Interview&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Audience Question 1: How to Deliver the First Impression Effectively in the Interview?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Audience Question 1: How to Deliver the First Impression Effectively in the Interview?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Panelists emphasized the importance of crafting a powerful first impression during academic job interviews. Think of this impression as a concise collection of keywords that represent you effectively. Here’s a breakdown:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keywords&lt;/strong&gt; : Your first impression should encapsulate key information, such as your name, university, major, and research interests. These are the fundamental elements that will help interviewers remember you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conciseness&lt;/strong&gt; : Keep it short and to the point. Long-winded introductions can dilute your message. Aim for clarity and brevity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Audience-Question-2-What-Is-the-Role-of-Networking&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Audience-Question-2-What-Is-the-Role-of-Networking&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Audience Question 2: What Is the Role of Networking?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Audience Question 2: What Is the Role of Networking?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Networking is a crucial element in your academic job search. It can significantly boost your chances of success by increasing your visibility and building connections within the academic community. Here are some key strategies to make the most of networking:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Attend Networking Events:&lt;/strong&gt; Actively participate in networking events, such as conference receptions, workshops, and seminars related to your field. These gatherings provide excellent opportunities to meet potential colleagues and employers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Initiate Conversations:&lt;/strong&gt; Don’t be passive during these events. Be proactive and engage in meaningful conversations with fellow attendees. Be open to discussing your research, interests, and goals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Leverage Conference Programs:&lt;/strong&gt; Take advantage of conference programs and directories to identify people you want to connect with. Prioritize those who share your research interests or work in institutions you’re interested in. You can use the conference’s app or website to contact them and propose a meeting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Audience-Question-3-Should-the-Future-Plan-in-the-Research-Statement-Be-General-and-Concise-or-Very-Detailed&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Audience-Question-3-Should-the-Future-Plan-in-the-Research-Statement-Be-General-and-Concise-or-Very-Detailed&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Audience Question 3: Should the Future Plan in the Research Statement Be General and Concise or Very Detailed?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Audience Question 3: Should the Future Plan in the Research Statement Be General and Concise or Very Detailed?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately the notes are missing for this question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Audience-Question-4-How-to-Determine-Desired-Qualities-in-Job-Ads-With-Varying-Specificity-e-g-Research-and-Teaching&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Audience-Question-4-How-to-Determine-Desired-Qualities-in-Job-Ads-With-Varying-Specificity-e-g-Research-and-Teaching&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Audience Question 4: How to Determine Desired Qualities in Job Ads With Varying Specificity (e.g., Research and Teaching)?&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Audience Question 4: How to Determine Desired Qualities in Job Ads With Varying Specificity (e.g., Research and Teaching)?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;One common challenge for job applicants is understanding what exactly a search committee is looking for in a candidate, especially when job postings vary in specificity. Getting a faculty position approved can be a daunting task for universities. Therefore, even when a job advertisement appears quite vague or general, you should still consider applying. Here’s why:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Broad Advertisements:&lt;/strong&gt; When a job ad is general in nature, it often indicates that the search committee is open to a wide range of candidates. This means you have a chance to throw your hat into the ring and showcase your unique skills, both in research and teaching.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tailoring for Targeted Ads:&lt;/strong&gt; On the other hand, when a job ad is highly specific, it’s crucial to align your application materials and interview responses with the stated requirements. Dr. Capan advises that you should meticulously tailor your documents and interview pitches to match the job description. This shows that you’ve done your homework and are genuinely interested in the role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Demonstrate Added Value:&lt;/strong&gt; Regardless of the ad’s specificity, you can also set yourself apart by illustrating what you can bring to the school. Highlight your unique qualities, ideas, or projects that could benefit the institution. Show them how you can be an asset, even if you don’t perfectly match every requirement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;My-Original-Notes&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#My-Original-Notes&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;My Original Notes&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;My Original Notes&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div id=&#34;NotesPics-MA60&#34; class=&#34;justified-gallery&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/MA60-Notes-1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 1&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/MA60-Notes-2.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 2&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/MA60-Notes-3.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 3&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/MA60-Notes-4.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 4&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/MA60-Notes-5.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 5&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/MA60-Notes-6.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 6&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/MA60-Notes-7.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 7&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/10/21/Crack-the-Academic-Job-Hunt-Code-Insider-Tips/MA60-Notes-8.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 8&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a style=&#34;background-color:black;color:white;text-decoration:none;padding:4px 6px;font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &amp;quot;San Francisco&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Ubuntu, Roboto, Noto, &amp;quot;Segoe UI&amp;quot;, Arial, sans-serif;font-size:12px;font-weight:bold;line-height:1.2;display:inline-block;border-radius:3px&#34; href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/@markuswinkler?utm_content=creditCopyText&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_source=unsplash&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; title=&#34;Download free do whatever you want high-resolution photos from Markus Winkler&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;&lt;svg xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; style=&#34;height:12px;width:auto;position:relative;vertical-align:middle;top:-2px;fill:white&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 32 32&#34;&gt;&lt;title&gt;unsplash-logo&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M10 9V0h12v9H10zm12 5h10v18H0V14h10v9h12v-9z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;thumbnail by Markus Winkler&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/06/07/Unlock-Your-Future-IS-Academic-Jobs-for-2023-2024/</guid>
            <title>Unlock Your Future: IS Academic Jobs for 2023-2024</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2023/06/07/Unlock-Your-Future-IS-Academic-Jobs-for-2023-2024/</link>
            <category>Job</category>
            <category>MIS</category>
            <category>IS</category>
            <category>Management Information Systems</category>
            <category>Information Systems</category>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 13:59:40 -0500</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;Are you ready to embark on a journey of professional growth and endless possibilities? &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Look no further! I am thrilled to present to you an exclusive list of IS academic jobs for the year 2023-2024. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re a seasoned professional or a fresh graduate eager to kickstart your career, these opportunities will ignite your passion and propel you towards success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/@kellysikkema?utm_source=unsplash&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&#34;&gt;Kelly Sikkema&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/photos/eNKrRic2wx0?utm_source=unsplash&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&#34;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2022/03/12/MIS-Conference-Calendar/</guid>
            <title>MIS Conference Calendar</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2022/03/12/MIS-Conference-Calendar/</link>
            <category>Research</category>
            <category>MIS</category>
            <category>IS</category>
            <category>Management Information Systems</category>
            <category>Information Systems</category>
            <category>Conference</category>
            <category>Calendar</category>
            <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2022 11:24:31 -0600</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;Stay on Top of MIS Conference Deadlines with Ease!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Discover the Convenience of my Reliable MIS Conference Calendar!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Photo by &lt;a href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/@charlesdeluvio?utm_source=unsplash&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&#34;&gt;charlesdeluvio&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/s/photos/calendar?utm_source=unsplash&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&#34;&gt;Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2021/04/03/Understanding-Bilibili-s-Business-Model/</guid>
            <title>Understanding Bilibili&#39;s Business Model</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2021/04/03/Understanding-Bilibili-s-Business-Model/</link>
            <category>Ph.D.</category>
            <category>Research</category>
            <category>Online Video Community</category>
            <category>Bilibili</category>
            <category>Business Model</category>
            <category>Video Collaboration</category>
            <category>哔哩哔哩</category>
            <category>B站</category>
            <category>商业模型</category>
            <category>联合投稿</category>
            <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 00:24:23 -0500</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;Bilibili is an iconic brand and a leading video community for young generations in China. This post includes my understadning and interpretation of Bilibili’s business model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;Introduction&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Introduction&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Introduction&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recent years have certified the rapid emergence and growth of online video communities, e.g. &lt;a href=&#34;https://youtube.com/&#34;&gt;YouTube.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/watch&#34;&gt;Facebook Watch&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tiktok.com/&#34;&gt;TikTok.com&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;, whose services mainly cover video publishing, experiencing, searching, commenting, tipping, marketing, and live-streaming through their Web-based platforms which are accessible via computers and mobile phones.&lt;br&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.limelight.com/resources/market-research/state-of-online-video-2020/&#34;&gt;Limelight’s market research&lt;/a&gt; towards online video in 2020, viewers spend nearly eight hours per week on average in watching various types of video content, and online video consumption has been enlarged across all age groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This post focuses on &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;, an iconic and leading online video community for young generations in China. From her &lt;a href=&#34;https://ir.bilibili.com/static-files/98bfad59-0a57-467c-a3f4-e250c3bada4b&#34;&gt;2020 annual report&lt;/a&gt;, on average she attracted 202 million monthly active users and 1.2 billion daily video views in the fourth quarter, 5.1 billion monthly interactions, and 5.6 million monthly video submissions by 1.8 million monthly active content creators. This enormous and flourishing pool of users and content creators ensures revenue generation from affiliated mobile games, membership subscription, tipping, advertising, and online shopping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Bilibili-com-An-Online-Video-Community&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Bilibili-com-An-Online-Video-Community&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Bilibili.com: An Online Video Community&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;Bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;: An Online Video Community&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this section, we dig into &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;, an iconic online video community for young Chinese generations, by approaching her from two aspects: an online video platform and a video-centered community.&lt;br&gt;The online video platform is where content creators publish their videos and users consume videos of their interest. And the social interactions among content creators and users consist of a video-centered community. Overall, an online video community is an online ecosystem among content creators and users around videos.&lt;br&gt;Then we graphically illustrate &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;‘s business model to demonstrate how &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; practices her commercialization efforts. Note that &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; provides mobile App and PC Website entrances, and we mainly exploit the mobile App in this post for clear demonstration and simplicity. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;An-Online-Video-Platform&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#An-Online-Video-Platform&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;An Online Video Platform&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;An Online Video Platform&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;justified-gallery&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/asplatform.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Platform&amp;#39;s Stakeholders: Users and Content Creators&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We walk through the details of how &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; operates as an online video platform in this section. As illustrated in the figure above, two main stakeholders get involved on this video platform: users and content creators. Content creators can upload their videos or start live-streaming, namely professional user generated video (PUGV), which are consumed by users. &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; also offers licensed contents, called occupationally generated videos (OGV), to users from third-party production companies, ranging from TV shows, movies, cartoon to anime.&lt;br&gt;Users can be categorized into three types. Viewers without registration can only watch PUGV.&lt;br&gt;Free registered membership gives users access to watch and comment in PUGV, follow and tip content creators, upload videos, and start live-streaming.&lt;br&gt;In addition to the free membership, premium membership comes with fees, allowing users to enjoy advanced PUGV (e.g., higher resolution, high dynamic range, Dolby audio), OGV, fancy comment emoji, and deals in mobile games and online shopping.&lt;br&gt;Note that content creators at least have free membership.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;justified-gallery&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/homepage.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;App Home Page&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above figure depicts the home page of &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;‘s mobile App. On the top, users can click the avatar and go to their profile page, search content of interests with keywords in the search box, and check private messages within the inbox.&lt;br&gt;At the bottom, five entrances appear.&lt;br&gt;The category page allows users to view content by predefined channels, e.g., anime, music, dance, video game, education, technology, daily life, food, animal, fashion, movies, and TV shows.&lt;br&gt;The feed page includes all content from users’ followed content creators and advertising.&lt;br&gt;The shopping page is a typical e-commerce site, supplying products related to anime, cartoons, and video games.&lt;br&gt;The profile page integrates users’ profile information, followers and followings, browsing history, favorites of content, uploaded content management, premium membership subscription, and App setting.&lt;br&gt;The rest of the home page is a video waterfall, i.e., a list of videos, which consists of banners, ordinary videos, sponsored videos, and advertising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;justified-gallery&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/videopage-nocol.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Description Section of A Video Page&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clicking on a video will be directed to a typical video page, demonstrated in the figure above. In the video description section, users can follow the focal content creator (e.g. CC1) and go to CC1’s personal page by clicking her avatar. CC1’s personal page has CC1’s basic information including self-introduction and numbers of followers and followings, and a list of all her uploaded videos. Users can also send feedback in the video page, e.g., like or dislike, tipping the focal content creator, adding the focal video into her favorites and sharing this video. The comment section functions as a discussion board, in which registered users can interact with each other by comments and replies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;A-Video-centered-Community&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#A-Video-centered-Community&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;A Video-centered Community&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;A Video-centered Community&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;justified-gallery&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/feedpage.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;App Feed Page&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; establishes its online community upon the social network between content creators and their followers, and discussion boards among users and content creators around videos.&lt;br&gt;Generally, users can click the follow button on a video display page or on the personal page of a content creator, as strong evidence of interest, to become a follower. By doing so, those followers will be notified on their mobile phones and feed page every time the followed content creator commits a new activity, e.g., tweets, live-streaming, or publishing a new video. In the feed page shown above, a user can browse all activities from her followed content creators ordered by posted time, and filter activities by tags. Moreover, a user can also post a tweet-like message, usually text with images, by clicking on the post button in the top-right corner. Note that a user can follow multiple content creators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;justified-gallery&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/videopage-cmt.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Discussion Section of A Video Page&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The figure above uncovers the discussion board (“comments” section) of a video display page.&lt;br&gt;For every uploaded video, all registered users, including content creators, can interact with others in the comment section by leaving comments, replying to others’ comments, providing feedback (like or dislike) on comments, or sharing comments.&lt;br&gt;Comments are in a popularity-ranked sequence by default, or can be ranked by posted time. Taking the top-ranked comment, posted by User 1, in the figure above for example, it is the most popular one since it receives the highest number of likes in this video’s comment section. CC and User 3 replied to User 1 directly, and User 2 responded to the CC’s reply. Each interaction (comment or reply) can be modeled as a directed edge from the sender to the receiver, in a network derived from the discussion board.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; provides one-to-one private messages among registered users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;Bilibili-com‘s-Business-Model&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Bilibili-com‘s-Business-Model&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Bilibili.com‘s Business Model&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;Bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;‘s Business Model&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;justified-gallery&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/bus-model.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;bilibili.com&amp;#39;s Business Model&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; operates this online video community to achieve her commercialization goal, explained in the previous figure.&lt;br&gt;Unregistered viewers come to &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; due to word-of-mouth (WOM) of funny content or searching for content of their interests. A multiple-choice quiz of 100 questions is mandatory to become a registered member without charge, within 60 minutes on community rules and knowledge about anime, cartoons, and video games. This membership exam hopes to ensure community etiquette, loyalty, and stickiness. Note that content creators at least have the free membership.&lt;br&gt;Registered users and content creators are retained by the online video community, i.e., interactions among content creators and users in social networks, and discussion boards around OGV and content creators’ uploaded PUGV.&lt;br&gt;Additionally, &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; provides auxiliary services for content creators, including influence and exposure promotion, monetization incentives, tutorials and seminars in video editing and recording, and data analysis for uploaded videos. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;‘s &lt;a href=&#34;https://ir.bilibili.com/static-files/98bfad59-0a57-467c-a3f4-e250c3bada4b&#34;&gt;2020 annual report&lt;/a&gt; says that the 3rd-month, 6th-month, 9th-month and 12th-month retention rate remained above 80%, for registered users who visited &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; in each month since 2018. The “retention rate” of users who visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; via mobile App or PC website in a given period, are to the percentage of these users who make at least one repeat visit after a certain duration; e.g., the “3rd-month retention rate” for users in a given month is the retention rate in the third month after the applicable month. &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; then extracted revenue from retained users with four major sources, including mobile games affiliation, value-added service (premium membership subscription and tipping), advertising, and e-commerce (online shopping).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apparently, the success of &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;‘s commercialization depends heavily on the community vibrancy and participation of retained users and content creators.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Video-Collaboration&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Video-Collaboration&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Video Collaboration&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Video Collaboration&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the goal of boosting her online video community vibrancy, a feature called video collaboration was newly introduced on &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;justified-gallery&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/videopage-col.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;A Collaborated Video Page&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to a video published by a single content creator, &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt; allows a team of content creators to collaborate on one video, whose display page shows all team members with usernames, avatars, roles labeled, following buttons, and links to their personal page.&lt;br&gt;The figure above shows the video display page of a collaborated video. For every team member, her personal page will exhibit this video, and all her followers will be notified of it once published via mobile phone notification and feed page. If a user follows multiple content creators in one team, this user will only receive one notification when this team newly publishes a video.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stakeholders in this online video community can be benefitted with good collaboration on video production.&lt;br&gt;For participated content creators, a wider set of video skills can bring impossible content to life, more creators’ labor can lead to better content quality, and more followers’ being notified can increase video exposure and the chance of receiving followers.&lt;br&gt;For the online video community, more followers’ being notified can contribute to community vibrancy by increasing the opportunity of interactions among content creators and users, and content creators in teams could establish belongingness and loyalty to the community by working together.&lt;br&gt;And for users, more of them can be entertained and retained because of high content quality and vivacious community environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that before the introduction of video collaboration on &lt;a href=&#34;https://bilibili.com/&#34;&gt;bilibili.com&lt;/a&gt;, content creators could still collaborate offline and upload their joint work by one content creator as the way of individual video production and display. For instance, the collaborated video in the figure above can be uploaded by only content creator CC1 as the way of individual video without video collaboration. However, the additional benefits, e.g., all team members, i.e., CC2 and CC3, listed on the video display page and every follower notified, are not available without the video collaboration characteristic.&lt;br&gt;To boot, without video collaboration, CC1, CC2, and CC3 can separately publish this video, resulting in its exhibition on their personal page as individual work, and every follower will be notified. However, by doing so, community vibrancy metrics are also separately calculated for three videos of the same content but different uploaders, which decreases total video performance, the chance of video exposure, and the opportunity of attracting new followers, compared to the collaborated version. And for users who only follow CC1 but not CC2 or CC3, video collaboration can inform them of CC2 and CC3, and these users may become new followers of CC2 and CC3.&lt;br&gt;Moreover, content creators in this team would establish additional belongingness and loyalty to the community by working together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a style=&#34;background-color:black;color:white;text-decoration:none;padding:4px 6px;font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &amp;quot;San Francisco&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Ubuntu, Roboto, Noto, &amp;quot;Segoe UI&amp;quot;, Arial, sans-serif;font-size:12px;font-weight:bold;line-height:1.2;display:inline-block;border-radius:3px&#34; href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/@victorhwn725?utm_source=unsplash&amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;utm_content=creditCopyText&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; title=&#34;Download free do whatever you want high-resolution photos from Victor He&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;&lt;svg xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; style=&#34;height:12px;width:auto;position:relative;vertical-align:middle;top:-2px;fill:white&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 32 32&#34;&gt;&lt;title&gt;unsplash-logo&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M10 9V0h12v9H10zm12 5h10v18H0V14h10v9h12v-9z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;thumbnail by Victor He&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/06/26/Understanding-BPR-COFISET-and-BPRH/</guid>
            <title>Understanding BPR, COFISET and BPRH</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/06/26/Understanding-BPR-COFISET-and-BPRH/</link>
            <category>Ph.D.</category>
            <category>Research</category>
            <category>Personalized Ranking</category>
            <category>Implicit Feedback</category>
            <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 21:53:11 -0500</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;BPR, COFISET, and BPRH all focus on collaborative filtering with matrix factorization and implicit feedbacks. This task is different from 5-star rating estimation in a sense that only some users’ action behaviors (e.g. purchase, view, like, dislike) are available. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This post includes my understanding of these three models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;TODO&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#TODO&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;TODO&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;TODO&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; BPR&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Backgrounds for COFISET&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Backgrounds for BPRH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; SGD for CIFISET and BPRH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Implementation codes for BPRH in Jupyter Notebook on a small and simple example&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;input checked=&#34;&#34; disabled=&#34;&#34; type=&#34;checkbox&#34;&gt; Full Implementation codes for BPRH&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;BPR&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#BPR&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;BPR&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;BPR&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;notification is-success is-size-6&#34;&gt;
 &lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt; UNDER CONSTRUCTION &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;Implementation&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Implementation&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Implementation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Implementation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may find several verions of BPR implementations below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jokingcoco/BPR_Bayesian-Personalized-Ranking_MPR_Multiple-Pairwise-Ranking&#34;&gt;https://github.com/jokingcoco/BPR_Bayesian-Personalized-Ranking_MPR_Multiple-Pairwise-Ranking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/valerystrizh/bpr&#34;&gt;https://github.com/valerystrizh/bpr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/lyst/lightfm&#34;&gt;https://github.com/lyst/lightfm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sh0416/bpr&#34;&gt;https://github.com/sh0416/bpr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/guoguibing/librec/search?q=BPR&amp;unscoped_q=BPR&#34;&gt;https://github.com/guoguibing/librec/search?q=BPR&amp;unscoped_q&amp;#x3D;BPR&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;COFISET&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#COFISET&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;COFISET&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;COFISET&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Item-sets-and-Pairwise-Preferences&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Item-sets-and-Pairwise-Preferences&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Item-sets and Pairwise Preferences&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Item-sets and Pairwise Preferences&lt;/h2&gt;

An item-set is a set of items. A user $u$&#39;s preference over an item-set is a function of $u$&#39;s preferences on items in this item-set. For example, $u$&#39;s preference on item-set $\mathcal{P}$ can be $\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P}} = |\mathcal{P}|^{-1} \sum_{i \in \mathcal{P}} \hat{r}_{ui}$. $\hat{r}_{ui}$ is $u$&#39;s estimated preference on item $i$.

A user $u$&#39;s pairwise preference  over two item-sets $\mathcal{P}, \mathcal{A}$ is defined as $\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}} = \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P}} - \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{A}}$. And in COFISET, the assumption of pairwise preference is $\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}} = \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P}} - \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{A}} &gt; 0, \mathcal{P} \subseteq \mathcal{I}^{tr}_{u}, \mathcal{A} \subseteq \mathcal{I}^{tr} \setminus \mathcal{I}^{tr}_{u}$. $\mathcal{P} \subseteq \mathcal{I}^{tr}_{u}$ is a set of items of observed feedback from user $u$ and $\mathcal{A} \subseteq \mathcal{I}^{tr} \setminus \mathcal{I}^{tr}_{u}$ is a set of items without observed feedback from user $u$.



&lt;h2 id=&#34;Objective-Function-and-Optimization&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Objective-Function-and-Optimization&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Objective Function and Optimization&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Objective Function and Optimization&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;COFISET’s relaxed optimization for all users is &lt;/p&gt;


$$ \min_{\Theta} \sum_{u \in \mathcal{U}^{tr}} \sum_{\mathcal{P} \subseteq \mathcal{I}_{u}^{tr}} \sum_{\mathcal{A} \subseteq \mathcal{I} \setminus \mathcal{I}_{u}^{tr}} \left[ \mathcal{L}(u, \mathcal{P}, \mathcal{A}) + \mathcal{R}(u, \mathcal{P}, \mathcal{A}) \right]  $$
, where $\Theta = \{ U_{u} \in \mathbb{R}^{ d \times 1}, V_{i} \in \mathbb{R}^{d \times 1}, b_i \in \mathbb{R}, u \in \mathcal{U}^{tr}, i \in \mathcal{I}^{tr} \}$ is the set of model parameter, the loss term $\mathcal{L}(u, \mathcal{P}, \mathcal{A}) = - \ln{\sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{P}\mathcal{A}})}$, $\sigma(z) = 1/(1+\exp{(-z)})$, the pairwise preferences of user $u$ across 2 item-sets $\mathcal{P}$ and $\mathcal{A}$ is $\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{P}\mathcal{A}} = \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{P}} - \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{A}}$, the estimated preferences of user $u$ on item-sets $\mathcal{P}$ and $\mathcal{A}$ are $\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{P}} = |P|^{-1} \sum_{i \in \mathcal{P}} \hat{r}_{ui}, \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{A}} = |A|^{-1} \sum_{j \in \mathcal{A}} \hat{r}_{uj}$, the estimated preference of user $u$ on item $i$ is $\hat{r}_{ui} = U_{u}^\top V_{i} + b_i$, and the regularization term $\mathcal{R}(u, \mathcal{P}, \mathcal{A}) = \frac{\alpha_u}{2} \| U_u \|^2 + \sum_{i \in \mathcal{P}} [\frac{\alpha_V}{2} \| V_i \|^2 + \frac{\beta_V}{2} b_i^2] + \sum_{j \in \mathcal{A}} [\frac{\alpha_V}{2} \| V_j \|^2 + \frac{\beta_V}{2} b_j^2]$.



&lt;h2 id=&#34;Corresponding-Gradients-in-SGD&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Corresponding-Gradients-in-SGD&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Corresponding Gradients in SGD&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Corresponding Gradients in SGD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stochastic gradient descent is applied in COFISET’s optimization. The corresponding gradients of model parameter $\Theta$ w.r.t. $\mathcal{L}(u, \mathcal{P}, \mathcal{A})$ and $\mathcal{R}(u, \mathcal{P}, \mathcal{A})$ are&lt;/p&gt;


$$ \begin{aligned} 
\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial U_{u}} &amp; = - \dfrac{\partial \ln \sigma}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma}{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}}{\partial U_{u}} \\ 
&amp; = - \sigma^{-1}(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (1-\sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}})) \dfrac{\partial (\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{P}} - \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{A}}) }{\partial U_{u}}\\ 
&amp; = - \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (|\mathcal{P}|^{-1} \sum_{i \in \mathcal{P}} V_{i} - |\mathcal{A}|^{-1} \sum_{j \in \mathcal{A}} V_{j} ) \\
&amp; = - \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (\overline{V}_{\mathcal{P}} - \overline{V}_{\mathcal{A}}), \forall u \in \mathcal{U}^{tr} \\ 
\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial U_u} &amp; = \alpha_{u} U_{u}, \forall u \in \mathcal{U}^{tr} \\
\end{aligned} $$






$$\begin{aligned}

\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial V_{i}} &amp; = - \dfrac{\partial \ln \sigma}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma}{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}}{\partial V_{i}} \\ 
&amp; = - \sigma^{-1}(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (1-\sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}})) \dfrac{\partial (\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{P}} - \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{A}}) }{\partial V_{i}}\\ 
&amp; = - \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (U_{u} / |\mathcal{P}|), \forall i \in \mathcal{P} \\
\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_i} &amp; = \alpha_{V} V_{i}, \forall i \in \mathcal{P} \\
\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial b_i} &amp; = - \dfrac{\partial \ln \sigma}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma}{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}}{\partial b_{i}} \\ 
&amp; = - \sigma^{-1}(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (1-\sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}})) \dfrac{\partial (\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{P}} - \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{A}}) }{\partial b_{i}}\\ 
&amp; = - \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) / |\mathcal{P}|, \forall i \in \mathcal{P} \\
\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_i} &amp; = \beta_V b_{i}, \forall i \in \mathcal{P} \\
\end{aligned} $$





$$\begin{aligned}

\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial V_j} &amp; = - \dfrac{\partial \ln \sigma}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma}{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}}{\partial V_{j}} \\ 
&amp; = - \sigma^{-1}(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (1-\sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}})) \dfrac{\partial (\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{P}} - \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{A}}) }{\partial V_{j}}\\ 
&amp; = \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (U_{u} / |\mathcal{A}|), \forall j \in \mathcal{A} \\
\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_j} &amp; = \alpha_{V} V_{j}, \forall j \in \mathcal{A} \\
\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial b_j} &amp; = - \dfrac{\partial \ln \sigma}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma}{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}}{\partial b_{j}} \\ 
&amp; = - \sigma^{-1}(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (1-\sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}})) \dfrac{\partial (\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{P}} - \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{A}}) }{\partial b_{j}}\\ 
&amp; = \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) / |\mathcal{A}|, \forall j \in \mathcal{A} \\
\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_j} &amp; = \beta_{V} b_{j}, \forall j \in \mathcal{A}
\end{aligned} $$



&lt;h3 id=&#34;Updating-Rules&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Updating-Rules&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Updating Rules&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Updating Rules&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Combining the gradients w.r.t. the loss term and the regularization term, the final gradients for each variable $U_{u}, V_{i}, V_{j}, b_{i}, b_{j}, u \in \mathcal{U}^{tr}, i \in \mathcal{P}, j \in \mathcal{A}$ are&lt;/p&gt;


$$ \begin{aligned}
	\nabla U_{u} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial U_{u}} + \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial U_{u}} \\ &amp; = - \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (\overline{V}_{\mathcal{P}} - \overline{V}_{\mathcal{A}}) + \alpha_{u} U_{u} \\
	\nabla V_{i} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial V_{i}} + \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_{i}} \\ &amp; = - \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (U_{u} / |\mathcal{P}|) + \alpha_{V} V_{i} \\
	\nabla V_{j} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial V_{j}} + \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_{j}} \\ &amp; = \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) (U_{u} / |\mathcal{A}|) + \alpha_{V} V_{j} \\
	\nabla b_{i} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial b_{i}} + \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_{i}} \\ &amp; = - \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) / |\mathcal{P}| + \beta_V b_{i}\\ 
	\nabla b_{j} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{L}}{\partial b_{j}} + \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_{j}} \\ &amp; = \sigma(-\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{P} \mathcal{A}}) / |\mathcal{A}| + \beta_{V} b_{j}
\end{aligned} $$
And the updating rules for each variable are

$$ \begin{aligned}
U_{u}^{t+1} &amp; = U_{u}^{t} - \gamma \nabla U_{u}^{t}, u \in \mathcal{U}^{tr} \\
V_{i}^{t+1} &amp; = V_{i}^{t} - \gamma \nabla V_{i}^{t}, i \in \mathcal{P} \\
V_{j}^{t+1} &amp; = V_{j}^{t} - \gamma \nabla V_{j}^{t}, j \in \mathcal{A} \\
b_{i}^{t+1} &amp; = b_{i}^{t} - \gamma \nabla b_{i}^{t}, i \in \mathcal{P} \\ 
b_{j}^{t+1} &amp; = b_{j}^{t} - \gamma \nabla b_{j}^{t}, j \in \mathcal{A}
\end{aligned} $$



&lt;h2 id=&#34;JAVA-Implementation&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#JAVA-Implementation&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;JAVA Implementation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;JAVA Implementation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may find the implementation of COFISET in this famous JAVA library of recommendation systems &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/guoguibing/librec/search?q=COFISET&amp;unscoped_q=COFISET&#34;&gt;LibRec&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;BPRH&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#BPRH&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;BPRH&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;BPRH&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Extended-Pairwise-Preferences&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Extended-Pairwise-Preferences&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Extended Pairwise Preferences&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Extended Pairwise Preferences&lt;/h2&gt;

Following COFISET, BPRH extends the pairwise preferences over item-sets. Besides the target action (e.g. purchase), a type of user&#39;s action called auxiliary action is introduced. Viewing, liking, and disliking are examples for auxiliary actions. Now the assumption of pairwise preferences in BPRH becomes $\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{I}} &gt; \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{J}} &gt; \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{K}}, \mathcal{I} \subseteq \mathcal{I}_{t}^{u}, \mathcal{J} \subseteq \mathcal{I}_{t}^{oa}, \mathcal{K} \subseteq \mathcal{I}_{n}^{u}$. $\mathcal{I} \subseteq \mathcal{I}_{t}^{u}$ is a set of items with target feedback from user $u$. $\mathcal{J} \subseteq \mathcal{I}_{t}^{oa}$ is a set of items with only auxiliary feedback from user $u$. And $\mathcal{K} \subseteq \mathcal{I}_{n}^{u}$ is a set of items without any observed feedback from user $u$. Then we can get $\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} &gt; 0, \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} &gt; 0$ for user $u$.



&lt;h2 id=&#34;Objective-Function-and-Optimization-1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Objective-Function-and-Optimization-1&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Objective Function and Optimization&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Objective Function and Optimization&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;BPRH reaches the maximization for all users $u$ as &lt;/p&gt;


	
	$$ \begin{aligned}
		\max_{\Theta} \quad &amp; f(\Theta) - \mathcal{R}(\Theta)
	\end{aligned}$$
	, where $f(\Theta) = \sum_{u \in U} \left\lbrace \sum_{ \mathcal{I} \subseteq I^{u}_{t}, \mathcal{J} \subseteq I^{u}_{oa} } {\ln \sigma \left( \dfrac{\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{I} \mathcal{J}} (\Theta) }{\alpha_{u}} \right) } + \sum_{ \mathcal{J} \subseteq I^{u}_{oa}, \mathcal{K} \subseteq I^{u}_{n}} {\ln \sigma \left( \hat{r}_{u \mathcal{J} \mathcal{K}} (\Theta) \right) } \right\rbrace$ is the negative value of loss term, $\Theta = \{ U_{u} \in \mathbb{R}^{1 \times d}, V_{i} \in \mathbb{R}^{1 \times d}, b_i \in \mathbb{R}, u \in \mathcal{U}, i \in I \}$ is the set of model parameter, the pairwise preference of user $u$ across 2 item-sets $\mathcal{I}$ and $\mathcal{J}$ is $\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} = \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}} - \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}}$,the pairwise preference of user $u$ across 2 item-sets $\mathcal{J}$ and $\mathcal{K}$ is $\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} = \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}} - \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{K}}$, the estimated preferences of user $u$ on item-sets $\mathcal{I}, \mathcal{J}, \mathcal{K}$ are $\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}} = |I|^{-1} \sum_{i \in \mathcal{I}} \hat{r}_{ui}$, $ \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}} = |J|^{-1} \sum_{j \in \mathcal{J}} \hat{r}_{uj}$, $\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{K}} = |K|^{-1} \sum_{k \in \mathcal{K}} \hat{r}_{uk}$, the estimated preference of user $u$ on item $i$ is $\hat{r}_{ui} = U_{u}^\top V_{i} + b_i$, and the regularization term $$ \begin{aligned}
		\mathcal{R}(\Theta) = \sum_{u \in U} \sum_{\mathcal{I} \subseteq I^{u}_{t}, \mathcal{J} \subseteq I^{u}_{oa}, \mathcal{K} \subseteq I^{u}_{n}} \{ &amp; \lambda_u \| U_{u} \|^2  \\ &amp; + \lambda_v \left( \| V_{\mathcal{I}} \|^2 + \| V_{\mathcal{J}} \|^2 + \| V_{\mathcal{K}} \|^2 \right) \\ &amp; + \lambda_b \left( b_{\mathcal{I}}^2 + b_{\mathcal{J}}^2 + b_{\mathcal{K}}^2 \right) \}
	\end{aligned}  $$, $V_{\mathcal{I}} = |\mathcal{I}|^{-1} \sum_{i \in \mathcal{I}} V_i$, $V_{\mathcal{J}} = |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \sum_{j \in \mathcal{J}} V_j$, $V_{\mathcal{K}} = |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} \sum_{k \in \mathcal{K}} V_k$, $b_{\mathcal{I}} = |\mathcal{I}|^{-1} \sum_{i \in \mathcal{I}} b_i$, $b_{\mathcal{J}} = |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \sum_{j \in \mathcal{J}} b_j$, $b_{\mathcal{K}} = |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} \sum_{k \in \mathcal{K}} b_k$. $\alpha_{u}$ is a parameter in $f(\Theta)$ controlling the contribution of $\hat{r}_{u \mathcal{I} \mathcal{J}} (\Theta)$ and calculated from data.
	


&lt;h2 id=&#34;Corresponding-Gradients-in-SGD-1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Corresponding-Gradients-in-SGD-1&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Corresponding Gradients in SGD&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Corresponding Gradients in SGD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stochastic gradient descent is utilized in optimization. The corresponding gradients of model parameter $\Theta$ w.r.t the negative loss term $f(\Theta)$ and the regularization term $\mathcal{R}(\Theta)$ are&lt;/p&gt;


$$\begin{aligned}
		\dfrac{\partial f}{\partial U_{u}} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} )  }{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} }{\partial U_{u}} + \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}})}{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} }{\partial U_{u}} \\ &amp; = \alpha_{u}^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_{u}^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) \left[ |I|^{-1} \sum_{i \in \mathcal{I}} V_{i} - |J|^{-1} \sum_{j \in \mathcal{J}} V_{j} \right] \\ &amp; + \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) \left[ |J|^{-1} \sum_{j \in \mathcal{J}} V_{j} - |K|^{-1} \sum_{k \in \mathcal{K}} V_{k} \right] \\ &amp; = \alpha_{u}^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_{u}^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) \left[ \overline{V}_{\mathcal{I}} - \overline{V}_{\mathcal{J}} \right] + \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) \left[ \overline{V}_{\mathcal{J}} - \overline{V}_{\mathcal{K}} \right], \forall u \in U \\
		\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial U_{u}} &amp; = 2 \lambda_{u} U_{u}, \forall u \in U\\
\end{aligned}$$

$$\begin{aligned}
		\dfrac{\partial f}{\partial V_{i}} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} )  }{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} }{\partial V_{i}} \\ &amp; = (|\mathcal{I}| \alpha_{u})^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_u^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) U_{u}, \forall i \in \mathcal{I}\\
		\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_{i}} &amp; = \lambda_{v} \dfrac{\partial \| V_{\mathcal{I}} \|^2 }{\partial V_{\mathcal{I}}} \dfrac{\partial V_{\mathcal{I}}}{\partial V_{i}} = 2 |\mathcal{I}|^{-1} \lambda_{v} V_{\mathcal{I}}, \forall i \in \mathcal{I} \\
		\dfrac{\partial f}{\partial b_{i}} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} )  }{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} }{\partial b_{i}} \\ &amp; = (|\mathcal{I}| \alpha_{u})^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_u^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ), \forall i \in \mathcal{I}\\
		\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_{i}} &amp; = \lambda_b \dfrac{\partial b_{\mathcal{I}}^2 }{\partial b_{\mathcal{I}}} \dfrac{\partial b_{\mathcal{I}}}{\partial b_{i}} = 2 \lambda_b |\mathcal{I}|^{-1} b_{\mathcal{I}}, \forall i \in \mathcal{I} \\ 
\end{aligned}$$
$$\begin{aligned}
		\dfrac{\partial f}{\partial V_{j}} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} )  }{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} }{\partial V_{j} } + \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}})}{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} }{\partial V_{j}} \\ &amp; = - ( |\mathcal{J}| \alpha_{u})^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_{u}^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) U_{u} + |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) U_{u} \\ &amp; = |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \left[ - \alpha_{u}^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_{u}^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) + \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) \right] U_{u}, \forall j \in \mathcal{J} \\
		\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_{j}} &amp; = \lambda_{v} \dfrac{\partial \| V_{\mathcal{J}} \|^2 }{\partial V_{\mathcal{J}}} \dfrac{\partial V_{\mathcal{J}}}{\partial V_{j}} = 2 |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \lambda_{v} V_{\mathcal{J}}, \forall j \in \mathcal{J}  \\
		\dfrac{\partial f}{\partial b_{j}} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} )  }{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} / \alpha_{u} }{\partial b_{j} } + \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}})}{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} }{\partial b_{j}} \\ &amp; = - ( |\mathcal{J}| \alpha_{u})^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_{u}^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) + |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) \\ &amp; = |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \left[ - \alpha_{u}^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_{u}^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) + \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) \right], \forall j \in \mathcal{J} \\
		\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_{j}} &amp; = \lambda_b \dfrac{\partial b_{\mathcal{J}}^2 }{\partial b_{\mathcal{J}}} \dfrac{\partial b_{\mathcal{J}}}{\partial b_{j}} = 2 \lambda_b |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} b_{\mathcal{J}}, \forall j \in \mathcal{J} \\
\end{aligned}$$
$$\begin{aligned}
		\dfrac{\partial f}{\partial V_{k}} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}})  }{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}}} \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} }{\partial V_{k}} \\ &amp; = - |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) U_{u}, \forall k \in \mathcal{K}\\
		\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_{k}} &amp; = \lambda_{v} \dfrac{\partial \| V_{\mathcal{K}} \|^2 }{\partial V_{\mathcal{K}}} \dfrac{\partial V_{\mathcal{K}}}{\partial V_{k}} = 2 |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} \lambda_{v} V_{\mathcal{K}}, \forall k \in \mathcal{K}\\
		\dfrac{\partial f}{\partial b_{k}} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial \ln(\sigma)}{\partial \sigma} \dfrac{\partial \sigma(\hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} )  }{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}}  } \dfrac{\partial \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}}  }{\partial b_{k}} \\ &amp; = - |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ), \forall k \in \mathcal{K}\\
		\dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_{k}} &amp; = \lambda_b \dfrac{\partial b_{\mathcal{K}}^2 }{\partial b_{\mathcal{K}}} \dfrac{\partial b_{\mathcal{K}}}{\partial b_{k}} = 2 \lambda_b |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} b_{\mathcal{K}}, \forall k \in \mathcal{K}\\
\end{aligned}$$



&lt;h3 id=&#34;Updating-Rules-1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Updating-Rules-1&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Updating Rules&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Updating Rules&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Combining the gradients w.r.t. the negative loss term and the regularization term, the final gradients for each variable $U_{u}, V_{i}, V_{j}, V_{k}, b_{i}, b_{j}, b_{k}, u \in U, i \in \mathcal{I}, j \in \mathcal{J}, k \in \mathcal{K}$ are&lt;/p&gt;


$$ \begin{aligned}
	\nabla U_{u} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial f}{\partial U_{u}} - \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial U_{u}} \\ &amp; = \alpha_{u}^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_{u}^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) \left[ \overline{V}_{\mathcal{I}} - \overline{V}_{\mathcal{J}} \right] + \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) \left[ \overline{V}_{\mathcal{J}} - \overline{V}_{\mathcal{K}} \right] - 2 \lambda_{u} U_{u}, \forall u \in U \\
	\nabla V_{i} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial f}{\partial V_{i}} - \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_{i}} \\ &amp; = (|\mathcal{I}| \alpha_{u})^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_u^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) U_{u} - 2 |\mathcal{I}|^{-1} \lambda_{v} V_{\mathcal{I}}, \forall i \in \mathcal{I}\\
	\nabla V_{j} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial f}{\partial V_{j}} - \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_{j}} \\ &amp; = |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \left[ - \alpha_{u}^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_{u}^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) + \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) \right] U_{u} - 2 |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \lambda_{v} V_{\mathcal{J}}, \forall j \in \mathcal{J}\\
	\nabla V_{k} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial f}{\partial V_{k}} - \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial V_{k}} \\ &amp; = - |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) U_{u} - 2 |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} \lambda_{v} V_{\mathcal{K}}, \forall k \in \mathcal{K}\\
	\nabla b_{i} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial f}{\partial b_{i}} - \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_{i}} \\ &amp; = (|\mathcal{I}| \alpha_{u})^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_u^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) - 2 \lambda_b |\mathcal{I}|^{-1} b_{\mathcal{I}}, \forall i \in \mathcal{I}\\ 
	\nabla b_{j} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial f}{\partial b_{j}} - \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_{j}} \\ &amp; = |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} \left[ - \alpha_{u}^{-1} \sigma(- \alpha_{u}^{-1} \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{I}\mathcal{J}} ) + \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) \right] - 2 \lambda_b |\mathcal{J}|^{-1} b_{\mathcal{J}}, \forall j \in \mathcal{J}\\
	\nabla b_{k} &amp; = \dfrac{\partial f}{\partial b_{k}} - \dfrac{\partial \mathcal{R}}{\partial b_{k}} \\ &amp; = - |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} \sigma(- \hat{r}_{u\mathcal{J}\mathcal{K}} ) - 2 \lambda_b |\mathcal{K}|^{-1} b_{\mathcal{K}}, \forall k \in \mathcal{K}\\
	\end{aligned} $$
	
	And the updating rules for each variable are
	
	$$ \begin{aligned}
	U_{u}^{t+1} &amp; = U_{u}^{t} + \gamma \nabla U_{u}^{t}, u \in U \\
	V_{i}^{t+1} &amp; = V_{i}^{t} + \gamma \nabla V_{i}^{t}, i \in \mathcal{I} \\
	V_{j}^{t+1} &amp; = V_{j}^{t} + \gamma \nabla V_{j}^{t}, j \in \mathcal{J} \\
	V_{k}^{t+1} &amp; = V_{k}^{t} + \gamma \nabla V_{k}^{t}, k \in \mathcal{K} \\
	b_{i}^{t+1} &amp; = b_{i}^{t} + \gamma \nabla b_{i}^{t}, i \in \mathcal{I} \\ 
	b_{j}^{t+1} &amp; = b_{j}^{t} + \gamma \nabla b_{j}^{t}, j \in \mathcal{J} \\
	b_{k}^{t+1} &amp; = b_{k}^{t} + \gamma \nabla b_{k}^{t}, k \in \mathcal{K}
	\end{aligned} $$



&lt;h2 id=&#34;Online-Updating-for-New-User&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Online-Updating-for-New-User&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Online Updating for New User&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Online Updating for New User&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rendle et al (2008) came with an online updating schema in their regularized kernal matrix factorization model along with stochastic gradient descent. Since BPRH also utilizes SGD in its objective function maximization, we can follow Rendle’s methods to update user and item matrices when a new user or item enters the landscape (cold-start problem). You can see the implementation code at &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/liu-yihong/BPRH/blob/master/bprH_gpu.py#L656&#34;&gt;bprH_gpu.py - Line 656&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;Python-Implementation&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Python-Implementation&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Python Implementation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Python Implementation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can star my BPRH repository and see the details of my BPRH implementation at &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/liu-yihong/BPRH&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github-readme-stats.vercel.app/api/pin/?username=liu-yihong&amp;repo=BPRH&amp;show_owner=true&#34; alt=&#34;BPRH Python Implementation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Reference&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Reference&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Reference&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Reference&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rendle, Steffen, et al. “BPR: Bayesian personalized ranking from implicit feedback.” arXiv preprint arXiv:1205.2618 (2012). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1205.2618&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pan, Weike, and Li Chen. “Cofiset: Collaborative filtering via learning pairwise preferences over item-sets.” Proceedings of the 2013 SIAM international conference on data mining. Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics, 2013. &lt;a href=&#34;https://epubs.siam.org/doi/abs/10.1137/1.9781611972832.20&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qiu, Huihuai, et al. “BPRH: Bayesian personalized ranking for heterogeneous implicit feedback.” Information Sciences 453 (2018): 80-98. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0020025516315742&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rendle, Steffen, and Lars Schmidt-Thieme. “Online-updating regularized kernel matrix factorization models for large-scale recommender systems.” Proceedings of the 2008 ACM conference on Recommender systems. 2008. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/1454008.1454047&#34;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/04/21/Yihong-MIS-Reading-List/</guid>
            <title>Yihong&#39;s MIS Ph.D. Reading List</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/04/21/Yihong-MIS-Reading-List/</link>
            <category>Ph.D.</category>
            <category>Research</category>
            <category>MIS</category>
            <category>IS</category>
            <category>Management Information Systems</category>
            <category>Information Systems</category>
            <category>Reading</category>
            <category>Publications</category>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 20:21:43 -0500</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;What to read as a &lt;strong&gt;Ph.D.&lt;/strong&gt; student major in &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Management Information Systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;notification is-success is-size-6&#34;&gt;
 &lt;button class=&#34;delete&#34;&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
 &lt;p style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;&lt;b&gt; KEEP UPDATING &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big ratio of papers listed here comes from MIS7420 Seminar in Management Information Systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ordered alphabetically, Prof. &lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/faculty/amit-mehra&#34;&gt;Amit Mehra&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/faculty/atanu-lahiri&#34;&gt;Atanu Lahiri&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/faculty/jianqing-chen&#34;&gt;Jianqing Chen&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/faculty/srinivasan-raghunathan&#34;&gt;Srinivasan Raghunathan&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/faculty/sumit-sarkar&#34;&gt;Sumit Sarkar&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/faculty/syam-menon&#34;&gt;Syam Menon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/faculty/vijay-mookerjee&#34;&gt;Vijay Mookerjee&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/faculty/zhiqiang-zheng&#34;&gt;Zhiqiang Zheng&lt;/a&gt; are in charge of this course and contribute a lot to this list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to thank them for creating a diverse topic portfolio which guides me through MIS landscape!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Journals&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Journals&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Journals&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Journals&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information Systems Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; (ISR) is an author-friendly peer-reviewed journal that publishes the best research in the information systems discipline. Its mission is to advance knowledge about the effective and efficient utilization of information technology by individuals, groups, organizations, society, and nations for the improvement of economic and social welfare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The journal covers a wide variety of phenomena and topics related to the design, management, use, valuation, and impact of information technologies at different levels of analysis. ISR publishes research that examines topics from a wide range of research traditions including cognitive psychology, economics, computer science, operations research, design science, organization theory, organization behavior, sociology, and strategic management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;footer&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INFORMS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.informs.org/Publications/INFORMS-Journals/Information-Systems-Research&#34;&gt;www.informs.org/Publications/INFORMS-Journals/Information-Systems-Research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Management Science&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is a scholarly journal that publishes scientific research on the practice of management focusing on the problems, interest, and concerns of managers. Within its scope are all aspects of management related to strategy, entrepreneurship, innovation, information technology, and organizations as well as all functional areas of business, such as accounting, finance, marketing, and operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;footer&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INFORMS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.informs.org/Publications/INFORMS-Journals/Management-Science&#34;&gt;www.informs.org/Publications/INFORMS-Journals/Management-Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MIS Quarterly&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;’s trifecta vision is to (1) achieve impact on scholarship and practice as the leading source of novel and accreted IS knowledge, (2) exhibit range in work published with respect to problem domains and stakeholders addressed as well as theoretical and methodological approaches used, and (3) execute effective editorial processes in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;footer&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MISQ&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.misq.org/&#34;&gt;www.misq.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UT Dallas’ Naveen Jindal School of Management has created a database to track publications in 24 leading business journals. The database contains titles and author affiliations of papers published in these journals since 1990. The information in the database is used to provide the top 100 business school rankings since 1990 based on the total contributions of faculty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;footer&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UTD24&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/the-utd-top-100-business-school-research-rankings/&#34;&gt;jindal.utdallas.edu/the-utd-top-100-business-school-research-rankings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Financial Times conducted a review in May 2016 of the journals that count towards its research rank. As a result, the number of journals considered went up to 50 compared to 45 previously.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;footer&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FT50&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ft.com/content/3405a512-5cbb-11e1-8f1f-00144feabdc0&#34;&gt;www.ft.com/content/3405a512-5cbb-11e1-8f1f-00144feabdc0&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;Conferences&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Conferences&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Conferences&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Conferences&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cistconf.org/&#34;&gt;Conference on Information Systems and Technology (CIST)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://aisel.aisnet.org/icis/&#34;&gt;International Conference on Information Systems (ICIS)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://wiseconf.org/&#34;&gt;Workshop on Information Systems and Economics (WISE)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://witsconf.org/&#34;&gt;Workshop on Information Technologies and Systems (WITS)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://teis-workshop.org/&#34;&gt;Theory in Economics of Information Systems (TEIS)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.scecr.org/&#34;&gt;Statistical Challenges in Electronic Commerce Research (SCECR)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rhsmith.umd.edu/centers-excellence/center-health-information-decision-systems/initiatives-programs/chita&#34;&gt;Conference on Health IT and Analytics (CHITA)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hicss.hawaii.edu/&#34;&gt;Hawaii International Conference on System Sciences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://cswimworkshop.org/&#34;&gt;China Summer Workshop on Information Management (CSWIM)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.informs.org/Meetings-Conferences/INFORMS-Conference-Calendar&#34;&gt;INFORMS Conference Calendar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Books-Papers-For-Reference&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Books-Papers-For-Reference&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Books &amp;amp; Papers For Reference&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Books &amp;amp; Papers For Reference&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Advice-Tips-for-PhD&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Advice-Tips-for-PhD&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Advice &amp;amp; Tips for PhD&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Advice &amp;amp; Tips for PhD&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Peters, Robert L. &lt;em&gt;Getting what you came for: the smart student’s guide to earning a master’s or a Ph. D&lt;/em&gt;. New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux, 1997. &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.macmillan.com/books/9780374524777/getting-what-you-came-for&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Booth, W. C., Booth, W. C., Colomb, G. G., Colomb, G. G., Williams, J. M., &amp;amp; Williams, J. M. (2003). “&lt;em&gt;The craft of research&lt;/em&gt;“. University of Chicago press. &lt;a href=&#34;https://press.uchicago.edu/ucp/books/book/chicago/C/bo23521678.html&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Andrej Karpathy, “&lt;em&gt;A Survival Guide to a PhD&lt;/em&gt;“, 2016. &lt;a href=&#34;http://karpathy.github.io/2016/09/07/phd/&#34;&gt;original source&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://web.archive.org/web/20200722074304/https://karpathy.github.io/2016/09/07/phd/&#34;&gt;web archive version&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sebastian Ruder, “&lt;em&gt;10 Tips for Research and a PhD&lt;/em&gt;“, 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ruder.io/10-tips-for-research-and-a-phd/index.html&#34;&gt;original source&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://web.archive.org/web/20200831140752/https://ruder.io/10-tips-for-research-and-a-phd/index.html&#34;&gt;web archive version&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phillips, Estelle, and Derek Pugh. “&lt;em&gt;How to Get a PhD: A Handbook for Students and their Supervisors&lt;/em&gt;“. McGraw-Hill Education (UK), 2015.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Li, Longxing. “The A-Z of the PhD Trajectory: A Practical Guide for a Successful Journey.” &lt;em&gt;International Journal of Teaching and Learning in Higher Education&lt;/em&gt; 32.3 (2020): 536-538. &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/book/10.1007/978-3-319-77425-1&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feibelman, Peter J. “&lt;em&gt;A PhD is not enough!: A guide to survival in science&lt;/em&gt;“. Basic Books, 2011.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Academic-Writings&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Academic-Writings&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Academic Writings&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Academic Writings&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cochrane, John H. “&lt;em&gt;Writing Tips for Ph. D. Students.&lt;/em&gt;“ Chicago, IL: University of Chicago, 2005. &lt;a href=&#34;http://mayoral.iae-csic.org/timeseries_bgse13/phd_paper_writing.pdf&#34;&gt;pdf&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zinsser, William. “On writing well: The classic guide to writing nonfiction.” &lt;em&gt;New York, NY&lt;/em&gt; (2006). &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.harpercollins.com/products/on-writing-well-william-zinsser&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sword, H. (2012).”&lt;em&gt;Stylish academic writing&lt;/em&gt;“. Harvard University Press. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hup.harvard.edu/catalog.php?isbn=9780674064485&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Swales, J.M. et al. “&lt;em&gt;Academic Writing for Graduate Students: Essential Tasks and Skills&lt;/em&gt;“. University of Michigan Press, 2012. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.press.umich.edu/2173936/academic_writing_for_graduate_students_3rd_edition&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wallwork, A. (2016). &lt;em&gt;“English for writing research papers”&lt;/em&gt;. Springer. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.springer.com/gp/book/9783319260921&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clark, R. P. (2008). &lt;em&gt;“Writing tools: 55 essential strategies for every writer”&lt;/em&gt;. Little, Brown Spark. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.littlebrownspark.com/titles/roy-peter-clark/writing-tools/9780316014991/&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clark, Roy Peter. &lt;em&gt;How to write short: Word craft for fast times&lt;/em&gt;. Little, Brown Spark, 2013. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.littlebrownspark.com/titles/roy-peter-clark/how-to-write-short/9780316204347/&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bailey, Stephen. &lt;em&gt;Academic writing: A handbook for international students&lt;/em&gt;. Routledge, 2014. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.routledge.com/Academic-Writing-A-Handbook-for-International-Students/Bailey/p/book/9781138048744&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Morley, John. “Academic phrasebank.” &lt;em&gt;Manchester: University of Manchester&lt;/em&gt; (2014). &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.phrasebank.manchester.ac.uk/&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;McCarthy, Michael, and Felicity O’dell. &lt;em&gt;Academic vocabulary in use&lt;/em&gt;. Ernst Klett Sprachen, 2008.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;INFOGRAPHIC: The secret to using tenses in scientific writing &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.editage.com/insights/the-secret-to-using-tenses-in-scientific-writing&#34;&gt;webpage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using tenses in scientific writing: Tense considerations for science writing &lt;a href=&#34;https://static1.squarespace.com/static/5f455f635c27d9245c08d8d3/t/5f710c752b388d20dacff3dd/1601244277474/Using_tenses_in_scientific_writing_Update_051112.pdf&#34;&gt;pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;Review-Writing&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Review-Writing&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Review Writing&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Review Writing&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elisabeth PainSep. 22, 2. (2016, September 22). “&lt;em&gt;How to review a paper&lt;/em&gt;“. Retrieved August 31, 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencemag.org/careers/2016/09/how-review-paper&#34;&gt;original source&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;http://web.archive.org/web/20200630062426/https://www.sciencemag.org/careers/2016/09/how-review-paper&#34;&gt;web archive version&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wiley. “&lt;em&gt;How to perform a peer review&lt;/em&gt;“. Retrieved August 31, 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://authorservices.wiley.com/Reviewers/journal-reviewers/how-to-perform-a-peer-review/index.html&#34;&gt;original source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Indiana University East. (2017). “&lt;em&gt;How to Write a Review of a Scholarly Article&lt;/em&gt;“. Retrieved August 31, 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.iue.edu/hss/writingcenter/documents/ReviewofaScholarlyArticle.pdf&#34;&gt;original source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adams, J. (2020, August 6). “&lt;em&gt;How to Write an Article Review&lt;/em&gt;“. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wikihow.com/Write-an-Article-Review&#34;&gt;original source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ahmed, B. S. (2018, February 26). “&lt;em&gt;Tips and advice when you review a scientific paper&lt;/em&gt;“. Elsevier. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.journals.elsevier.com/applied-soft-computing/news/tips-and-advice-when-you-review-a-scientific-paper&#34;&gt;original source&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MIS Quarterly. (2020). “&lt;em&gt;Reviewing for MIS Quarterly: Virtuous Reviewing at MIS Quarterly&lt;/em&gt;“. &lt;a href=&#34;https://misq.org/reviews/&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Academic-Presentations&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Academic-Presentations&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Academic Presentations&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Academic Presentations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reinhart, Susan M. &lt;em&gt;Giving academic presentations&lt;/em&gt;. Ann Arbor, MI: University of Michigan Press, 2002. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.press.umich.edu/11918183/giving_academic_presentations_second_edition&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chivers, Barbara, and Michael Shoolbred. &lt;em&gt;A Student′ s Guide to Presentations: Making your Presentation Count&lt;/em&gt;. Sage, 2007. &lt;a href=&#34;https://us.sagepub.com/en-us/nam/a-students-guide-to-presentations/book226241&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graham Burton. &lt;em&gt;Presenting: Deliver Academic Presentations with Confidence&lt;/em&gt; HarperCollins UK, 2014.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rendle-Short, Johanna. &lt;em&gt;The academic presentation: Situated talk in action&lt;/em&gt;. Routledge, 2016.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nycyk, Michael. “Academic and scientific poster presentation: a modern comprehensive guide.” (2018): 1550-1552.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Statistics-and-Probability&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Statistics-and-Probability&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Statistics and Probability&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Statistics and Probability&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Casella, George, and Roger L. Berger. Statistical inference. Vol. 2. Pacific Grove, CA: Duxbury, 2002.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Optimization&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Optimization&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Optimization&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Optimization&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Boyd, Stephen, Stephen P. Boyd, and Lieven Vandenberghe. Convex optimization. Cambridge university press, 2004. &lt;a href=&#34;https://web.stanford.edu/~boyd/cvxbook/bv_cvxbook.pdf&#34;&gt;[pdf]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sundaram, Rangarajan K. A first course in optimization theory. Cambridge university press, 1996.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Microeconomic&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Microeconomic&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Microeconomic&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Microeconomic&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Varian, Hal R. Microeconomic analysis. WW Norton, 1992.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rubinstein, Ariel. Lecture notes in microeconomic theory: the economic agent. Princeton University Press, 2012. &lt;a href=&#34;http://arielrubinstein.tau.ac.il/books.html&#34;&gt;[pdf]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Econometrics&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Econometrics&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Econometrics&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Econometrics&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Greene, William H. Econometric analysis (Eight Edition). (2017).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cameron, A. Colin, and Pravin K. Trivedi. Microeconometrics: methods and applications. Cambridge university press, 2005.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wooldridge, Jeffrey M. Econometric analysis of cross section and panel data. MIT press, 2010.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wooldridge, Jeffrey M. Introductory econometrics: A modern approach. Nelson Education, 2016.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hill, R. Carter, William E. Griffiths, and Guay C. Lim. Principles of econometrics. John Wiley &amp;amp; Sons, 2018.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Davidson, Russell, and James G. MacKinnon. Econometric theory and methods. Vol. 5. New York: Oxford University Press, 2004.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maddala, Gangadharrao S. Limited-dependent and qualitative variables in econometrics. No. 3. Cambridge university press, 1986.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Angrist, Joshua D., and Jörn-Steffen Pischke. Mostly harmless econometrics: An empiricist’s companion. Princeton university press, 2008.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baltagi, Badi Hani. “&lt;em&gt;Econometric analysis of panel data&lt;/em&gt;“. Springer International Publishing, (6th Edition, 2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/book/10.1007/978-3-030-53953-5&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;article class=&#34;message message-immersive is-primary&#34;&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-cube&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; This &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bradyneal.com/which-causal-inference-book&#34;&gt;Wikipedia page&lt;/a&gt; compares technical information for a number of statistical analysis packages.
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;Causal-Inference&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Causal-Inference&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Causal Inference&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Causal Inference&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;article class=&#34;message message-immersive is-primary&#34;&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-blog&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Brady Neal&#39;s blog provides &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bradyneal.com/which-causal-inference-book&#34;&gt;a good list&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-book&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Brady Neal&#39;s blog also provides a good course &#34;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bradyneal.com/causal-inference-course&#34;&gt;Introduction to Causal Inference&lt;/a&gt;&#34;.
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pearl, Judea. “&lt;em&gt;Causal inference in statistics: An overview.&lt;/em&gt;“ Statistics surveys 3 (2009): 96-146. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ftp.cs.ucla.edu/pub/stat_ser/r350.pdf&#34;&gt;pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yao, Liuyi, et al. “&lt;em&gt;A survey on causal inference.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:2002.02770 (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2002.02770&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Game-Theory&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Game-Theory&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Game Theory&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Game Theory&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gibbons, Robert S. Game theory for applied economists. Princeton University Press, 1992.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fudenberg, Drew, and Jean Tirole. Game theory. MIT press, 1991.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Myerson, Roger B. Game Theory: Analysis of Conflict. Harvard university press, 2013.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Osborne, Martin J., and Ariel Rubinstein. A course in game theory. MIT press, 1994.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Industry-Organization&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Industry-Organization&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Industry Organization&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Industry Organization&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tirole, Jean. The theory of industrial organization. MIT press, 1988.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vives, Xavier. Oligopoly pricing: old ideas and new tools. MIT press, 1999.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Martin, Stephen. Advanced industrial economics. Blackwell Publishers, 2002.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Belleflamme, Paul, and Martin Peitz. &lt;em&gt;Industrial organization: markets and strategies&lt;/em&gt;. Cambridge University Press, 2015.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Machine-Learning-Deep-Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Machine-Learning-Deep-Learning&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Machine Learning &amp;#x2F; Deep Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Machine Learning &amp;#x2F; Deep Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;article class=&#34;message message-immersive is-primary&#34;&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-book&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Sergey Levine provides a course CS W182 / 282A - UC Berkeley at &lt;a href=&#34;https://cs182sp21.github.io/&#34;&gt;Designing, Visualizing and Understanding Deep Neural Networks&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;
- Hastie, Trevor, Robert Tibshirani, and Jerome Friedman. The elements of statistical learning: data mining, inference, and prediction. Springer Science &amp; Business Media, 2009. [source](https://web.stanford.edu/~hastie/ElemStatLearn/)
- Bishop, Christopher M. Pattern recognition and machine learning. springer, 2006. [pdf](https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/research/uploads/prod/2006/01/Bishop-Pattern-Recognition-and-Machine-Learning-2006.pdf)
- Barber, David. Bayesian reasoning and machine learning. Cambridge University Press, 2012. [source](http://web4.cs.ucl.ac.uk/staff/D.Barber/pmwiki/pmwiki.php?n=Brml.Online)
- Murphy, Kevin P. Machine learning: a probabilistic perspective. MIT press, 2012.
- Goodfellow, Ian, Yoshua Bengio, and Aaron Courville. &#34;Deep learning.&#34; Cambridge: MIT press, 2016. [source](https://www.deeplearningbook.org/)

&lt;h2 id=&#34;Few-shot-Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Few-shot-Learning&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Few-shot Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Few-shot Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wang, Yaqing, et al. “Generalizing from a few examples: A survey on few-shot learning.” &lt;em&gt;ACM Computing Surveys (CSUR)&lt;/em&gt; 53.3 (2020): 1-34. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3386252&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Transfer-Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Transfer-Learning&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Transfer Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Transfer Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pan, Sinno Jialin, and Qiang Yang. “A survey on transfer learning.” &lt;em&gt;IEEE Transactions on knowledge and data engineering&lt;/em&gt; 22.10 (2009): 1345-1359. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/5288526&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weiss, Karl, Taghi M. Khoshgoftaar, and DingDing Wang. “A survey of transfer learning.” &lt;em&gt;Journal of Big data&lt;/em&gt; 3.1 (2016): 1-40. &lt;a href=&#34;https://journalofbigdata.springeropen.com/articles/10.1186/s40537-016-0043-6&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tan, Chuanqi, et al. “A survey on deep transfer learning.” &lt;em&gt;International conference on artificial neural networks&lt;/em&gt;. Springer, Cham, 2018. &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-030-01424-7_27&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zhuang, Fuzhen, et al. “A comprehensive survey on transfer learning.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the IEEE&lt;/em&gt; 109.1 (2020): 43-76. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/9134370&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Reinforcement-Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Reinforcement-Learning&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Reinforcement Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Reinforcement Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;article class=&#34;message message-immersive is-primary&#34;&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fab fa-github&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; datawhalechina on github.com provides a course in Chinese at &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/datawhalechina/easy-rl&#34;&gt;datawhalechina/easy-rl&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fab fa-github&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Bolei Zhou on github.com provides a course in English at &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/zhoubolei/introRL&#34;&gt;zhoubolei/introRL&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-book&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; DeepMind and UCL provide an introduction lecture on reinforcement learning at &lt;a href=&#34;https://deepmind.com/learning-resources/reinforcement-learning-series-2021&#34;&gt;Reinforcement Learning Lecture Series 2021&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-book&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Hao Dong, Zihan Ding and Shanghang Zhang offer an online version of the book &lt;a href=&#34;https://deepreinforcementlearningbook.org/&#34;&gt;&#34;Deep Reinforcement Learning: Fundamentals, Research and Applications&#34;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sutton, Richard S., and Andrew G. Barto. Reinforcement learning: An introduction. MIT press, 2018. &lt;a href=&#34;http://incompleteideas.net/book/RLbook2020.pdf&#34;&gt;pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yang, Tianpei, et al. “Exploration in deep reinforcement learning: A comprehensive survey.” &lt;em&gt;arXiv preprint arXiv:2109.06668&lt;/em&gt; (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2109.06668&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Stochastic-Differential-Equation&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Stochastic-Differential-Equation&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Stochastic Differential Equation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Stochastic Differential Equation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gardiner, Crispin W. “&lt;em&gt;Handbook of stochastic methods: for physics, chemistry and the natural sciences.&lt;/em&gt;“ (2004). &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.springer.com/gp/book/9783540707127&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dixit, Robert K., and Robert S. Pindyck. “&lt;em&gt;Investment under uncertainty&lt;/em&gt;“. Princeton university press, 2012. &lt;a href=&#34;https://press.princeton.edu/books/hardcover/9780691034102/investment-under-uncertainty&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Klebaner, Fima C. “&lt;em&gt;Introduction to stochastic calculus with applications&lt;/em&gt;“. World Scientific Publishing Company, 2012. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.worldscientific.com/worldscibooks/10.1142/p821&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Evans, Lawrence C. “&lt;em&gt;An introduction to stochastic differential equations&lt;/em&gt;“. Vol. 82. American Mathematical Soc., 2012. &lt;a href=&#34;http://ft-sipil.unila.ac.id/dbooks/AN%20INTRODUCTION%20TO%20STOCHASTIC%20DIFFERENTIAL%20EQUATIONS%20VERSION%201.2.pdf&#34;&gt;pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mikosch, Thomas. “&lt;em&gt;Elementary stochastic calculus with finance in view&lt;/em&gt;“. World scientific, 1998. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.worldscientific.com/worldscibooks/10.1142/3856&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oksendal, Bernt. “&lt;em&gt;Stochastic differential equations: an introduction with applications&lt;/em&gt;“. Springer Science &amp;amp; Business Media, 2013. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.springer.com/gp/book/9783662036204&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mao, Xuerong. “&lt;em&gt;Stochastic differential equations and applications&lt;/em&gt;“. Elsevier, 2007. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.elsevier.com/books/stochastic-differential-equations-and-applications/mao/978-1-904275-34-3&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Analytical-Model&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Analytical-Model&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Analytical Model&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Analytical Model&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;How-to-Model&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#How-to-Model&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;How to Model&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;How to Model&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Varian, Hal R. “&lt;em&gt;How to build an economic model in your spare time.&lt;/em&gt;“ The American Economist 61.1 (2016): 81-90. &lt;a href=&#34;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/pdf/10.1177/0569434515627089&#34;&gt;pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Bounded-Rationality-and-Attention&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Bounded-Rationality-and-Attention&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Bounded Rationality and Attention&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Bounded Rationality and Attention&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gifford, Sharon. “&lt;em&gt;Limited attention as the bound on rationality.&lt;/em&gt;“ The BE Journal of Theoretical Economics 5.1 (2005). &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.degruyter.com/view/journals/bejte/5/1/article-bejte.2005.5.1.1108.xml.xml&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Adverse-Selection-and-Self-Selection&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Adverse-Selection-and-Self-Selection&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Adverse Selection and Self Selection&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Adverse Selection and Self Selection&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Akerlof, George A. “&lt;em&gt;The market for “lemons”: Quality uncertainty and the market mechanism.&lt;/em&gt;“ Uncertainty in economics. Academic Press, 1978. 235-251. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/B978012214850750022X&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sundararajan, Arun. “&lt;em&gt;Nonlinear pricing of information goods.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management science 50.12 (2004): 1660-1673. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.1040.0291&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Two-sided-Market&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Two-sided-Market&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Two-sided Market&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Two-sided Market&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tunc, Murat M., Huseyin Cavusoglu, and Srinivasan Raghunathan. “&lt;em&gt;Two-Sided Adverse Selection and Bilateral Reviews in Sharing Economy.&lt;/em&gt;“ Available at SSRN 3499979 (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3499979&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manlu Chen, Ming Hu, Jianfu Wang (2022) Food Delivery Service and Restaurant: Friend or Foe?. Management Science 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/mnsc.2021.4245&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Externalities&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Externalities&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Externalities&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Externalities&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;August, Terrence, and Tunay I. Tunca. “&lt;em&gt;Network software security and user incentives.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science 52.11 (2006): 1703-1720. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.1060.0568&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Koh, Byungwan, Srinivasan Raghunathan, and Barrie R. Nault. “&lt;em&gt;Is voluntary profiling welfare enhancing?.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Information Systems Quarterly, Forthcoming (2015). &lt;a href=&#34;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2841845&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Platform-Openness&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Platform-Openness&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Platform Openness&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Platform Openness&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adner, Ron, Jianqing Chen, and Feng Zhu. “&lt;em&gt;Frenemies in platform markets: Heterogeneous profit foci as drivers of compatibility decisions.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2019.3327&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chen, Jianqing, and Zhiling Guo. “&lt;em&gt;New media advertising and retail platform openness.&lt;/em&gt;“ &lt;a href=&#34;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2694073&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Versioning&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Versioning&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Versioning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Versioning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhargava, Hemant K., and Vidyanand Choudhary. “&lt;em&gt;Information goods and vertical differentiation.&lt;/em&gt;“ Journal of Management Information Systems 18.2 (2001): 89-106. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/07421222.2001.11045681&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lahiri, Atanu, and Debabrata Dey. “&lt;em&gt;Versioning and information dissemination: A new perspective.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research 29.4 (2018): 965-983. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2017.0763&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Contracting-and-Moral-Hazard&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Contracting-and-Moral-Hazard&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Contracting and Moral Hazard&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Contracting and Moral Hazard&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cezar, Asunur, Huseyin Cavusoglu, and Srinivasan Raghunathan. “&lt;em&gt;Outsourcing information security: Contracting issues and security implications.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science 60.3 (2014): 638-657. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2013.1763&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choudhary, Vidyanand, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Personalized pricing and quality differentiation.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science 51.7 (2005): 1120-1130. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.1050.0383&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Information-Goods&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Information-Goods&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Information Goods&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Information Goods&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;Security&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Security&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Security&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Security&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dey, Debabrata, Atanu Lahiri, and Guoying Zhang. “&lt;em&gt;Hacker behavior, network effects, and the security software market.&lt;/em&gt;“ Journal of Management Information Systems 29.2 (2012): 77-108. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.2753/MIS0742-1222290204&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ghoshal, Abhijeet, Atanu Lahiri, and Debabrata Dey. “&lt;em&gt;Drawing a Line in the Sand: Commitment Problem in Ending Software Support.&lt;/em&gt;“ MIS Quarterly 41.4 (2017): 1227-1247. &lt;a href=&#34;https://misq.org/drawing-a-line-in-the-sand-commitment-problem-in-ending-software-support.html&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Piracy&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Piracy&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Piracy&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Piracy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lahiri, Atanu, and Debabrata Dey. “&lt;em&gt;Effects of piracy on quality of information goods.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science 59.1 (2013): 245-264. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.1120.1578&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim, Antino, Atanu Lahiri, and Debabrata Dey. “&lt;em&gt;The” Invisible Hand” of Piracy: An Economic Analysis of the Information-Goods Supply Chain.&lt;/em&gt;“ MIS Quarterly 42.4 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://misq.org/the-invisible-hand-of-piracy-an-economic-analysis-of-the-information-goods-supply-chain.html&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chellappa, Ramnath K., and Shivendu Shivendu. “&lt;em&gt;Managing piracy: Pricing and sampling strategies for digital experience goods in vertically segmented markets.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research 16.4 (2005): 400-417. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/10.1287/isre.1050.0069&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jain, Sanjay. “&lt;em&gt;Digital piracy: A competitive analysis.&lt;/em&gt;“ Marketing science 27.4 (2008): 610-626. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mksc.1070.0313&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peitz, Martin, and Patrick Waelbroeck. “&lt;em&gt;Piracy of digital products: A critical review of the theoretical literature.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Economics and Policy 18.4 (2006): 449-476. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0167624506000540&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Online-Advertising-and-Keyword-Auctions&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Online-Advertising-and-Keyword-Auctions&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Online Advertising and Keyword Auctions&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Online Advertising and Keyword Auctions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chen, Jianqing, and Jan Stallaert. “&lt;em&gt;An economic analysis of online advertising using behavioral targeting.&lt;/em&gt;“ Mis Quarterly 38.2 (2014): 429-A7. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jstor.org/stable/26634933&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liu, De, Jianqing Chen, and Andrew B. Whinston. “&lt;em&gt;Ex ante information and the design of keyword auctions.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research 21.1 (2010): 133-153.&lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.1080.0225&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Counterfeit-Seller&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Counterfeit-Seller&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Counterfeit Seller&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Counterfeit Seller&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;Recommendation-Systems&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Recommendation-Systems&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Recommendation Systems&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Recommendation Systems&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghoshal, Abhijeet, Vijay S. Mookerjee, and Sumit Sarkar. “&lt;em&gt;Recommendations and Cross-selling: Pricing Strategies when Personalizing Firms Cross-sell.&lt;/em&gt;“ Journal of Management Information Systems 38.2 (2021): 430-456. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/07421222.2021.1912930&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Empirical-Model&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Empirical-Model&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Empirical Model&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Empirical Model&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Targeting-with-Mobile-Coupons&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Targeting-with-Mobile-Coupons&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Targeting with Mobile Coupons&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Targeting with Mobile Coupons&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghose, Anindya, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Seizing the commuting moment: Contextual targeting based on mobile transportation apps.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research 30.1 (2019): 154-174. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2018.0792&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Andrews, Michelle, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Mobile ad effectiveness: Hyper-contextual targeting with crowdedness.&lt;/em&gt;“ Marketing Science 35.2 (2016): 218-233. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mksc.2015.0905&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Subscription-Models-in-Online-Platforms&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Subscription-Models-in-Online-Platforms&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Subscription Models in Online Platforms&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Subscription Models in Online Platforms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oestreicher-Singer, Gal, and Lior Zalmanson. “&lt;em&gt;Content or community? A digital business strategy for content providers in the social age.&lt;/em&gt;“ MIS quarterly (2013): 591-616. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jstor.org/stable/43825924&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bapna, Ravi, and Akhmed Umyarov. “&lt;em&gt;Do your online friends make you pay? A randomized field experiment on peer influence in online social networks.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science 61.8 (2015): 1902-1920. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2014.2081&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Multichannel-Advertising-and-Retailing&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Multichannel-Advertising-and-Retailing&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Multichannel Advertising and Retailing&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Multichannel Advertising and Retailing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kumar, Anuj, Amit Mehra, and Subodha Kumar. “&lt;em&gt;Why do stores drive online sales? Evidence of underlying mechanisms from a multichannel retailer.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research 30.1 (2019): 319-338. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2018.0814&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghose, Anindya, and Vilma Todri. “&lt;em&gt;Towards a digital attribution model: Measuring the impact of display advertising on online consumer behavior.&lt;/em&gt;“ Available at SSRN 2672090 (2015). &lt;a href=&#34;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2672090&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Video-Advertising-and-Recommendations&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Video-Advertising-and-Recommendations&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Video Advertising and Recommendations&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Video Advertising and Recommendations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kumar, Anuj, and Yinliang Tan. “&lt;em&gt;The demand effects of joint product advertising in online videos.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science 61.8 (2015): 1921-1937. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2014.2086&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kumar, Anuj, and Kartik Hosanagar. “&lt;em&gt;Measuring the value of recommendation links on product demand.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research 30.3 (2019): 819-838. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2018.0833&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Matthew McGranaghan, Jura Liaukonyte, Kenneth C. Wilbur (2022) How Viewer Tuning, Presence, and Attention Respond to Ad Content and Predict Brand Search Lift. Marketing Science 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/mksc.2021.1344&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Educational-Technology&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Educational-Technology&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Educational Technology&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Educational Technology&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kumar, Anuj, and Amit Mehra. “&lt;em&gt;Remedying Education with Personalized Homework: Evidence from a Randomized Field Experiment in India.&lt;/em&gt;“ Available at SSRN 2756059 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2756059&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Machine-Learning-Applications&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Machine-Learning-Applications&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Machine Learning Applications&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Machine Learning Applications&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wang, Quan, Beibei Li, and Param Vir Singh. “&lt;em&gt;Copycats vs. original mobile apps: A machine learning copycat-detection method and empirical analysis.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research 29.2 (2018): 273-291. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2017.0735&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Burtch, Gordon, Anindya Ghose, and Sunil Wattal. “&lt;em&gt;The hidden cost of accommodating crowdfunder privacy preferences: A randomized field experiment.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science 61.5 (2015): 949-962. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2014.2069&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vítor Albiero, and Kevin W. Bowyer. “&lt;em&gt;Is Face Recognition Sexist? No, Gendered Hairstyles and Biology Are&lt;/em&gt;“  BMVC 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2008.06989&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Piracy-1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Piracy-1&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Piracy&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Piracy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Martin Eisend. “&lt;em&gt;Explaining Digital Piracy: A Meta-Analysis.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research 30.2 (2019): 636-664. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/10.1287/isre.2018.0821&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Christian Peukert, Stefan Bechtold, Michail Batikas, Tobias Kretschmer (2022) Regulatory Spillovers and Data Governance: Evidence from the GDPR. Marketing Science 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/mksc.2021.1339&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Algorithm-Concern&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Algorithm-Concern&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Algorithm Concern&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Algorithm Concern&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lambrecht, Anja, and Catherine Tucker. “&lt;em&gt;Algorithmic bias? An empirical study of apparent gender-based discrimination in the display of STEM career ads&lt;/em&gt;.” Management Science 65.7 (2019): 2966-2981. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2018.3093&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dietvorst, Berkeley J., Joseph P. Simmons, and Cade Massey. “&lt;em&gt;Overcoming algorithm aversion: People will use imperfect algorithms if they can (even slightly) modify them&lt;/em&gt;.” Management Science 64.3 (2018): 1155-1170. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2016.2643&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kleinberg, Jon, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Human decisions and machine predictions&lt;/em&gt;.” The quarterly journal of economics 133.1 (2018): 237-293. &lt;a href=&#34;https://academic.oup.com/qje/article/133/1/237/4095198&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Athey, Susan. “&lt;em&gt;The impact of machine learning on economics&lt;/em&gt;.” The economics of artificial intelligence: An agenda. University of Chicago Press, 2018. 507-547. &lt;a href=&#34;https://projects.iq.harvard.edu/files/pegroup/files/athey2018.pdf&#34;&gt;pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bouayad, Lina, Balaji Padmanabhan, and Kaushal Chari. “&lt;em&gt;Audit Policies Under the Sentinel Effect: Deterrence-Driven Algorithms&lt;/em&gt;.” Information Systems Research 30.2 (2019): 466-485. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2019.0841&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Germann, Maximilian, and Christoph Merkle. “&lt;em&gt;Algorithm Aversion in Financial Investing&lt;/em&gt;.” Available at SSRN 3364850 (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3364850&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Empirical-Methodology&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Empirical-Methodology&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Empirical Methodology&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Empirical Methodology&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bertrand, Marianne, Esther Duflo, and Sendhil Mullainathan. “How much should we trust differences-in-differences estimates?.” The Quarterly journal of economics 119.1 (2004): 249-275. &lt;a href=&#34;https://academic.oup.com/qje/article/119/1/249/1876068&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tafti, Ali R., and Galit Shmueli. “Beyond Overall Treatment Effects: Leveraging Covariates in Randomized Experiments Guided by Causal Structure.” Available at SSRN 3331772 (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=3331772&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xu, Yiqing. “&lt;em&gt;Generalized synthetic control method: Causal inference with interactive fixed effects models.&lt;/em&gt;“ Political Analysis 25.1 (2017): 57-76.&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/political-analysis/article/generalized-synthetic-control-method-causal-inference-with-interactive-fixed-effects-models/B63A8BD7C239DD4141C67DA10CD0E4F3&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rubin, Donald B., and Richard P. Waterman. “&lt;em&gt;Estimating the causal effects of marketing interventions using propensity score methodology&lt;/em&gt;.” Statistical Science (2006): 206-222. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jstor.org/stable/27645750&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Athey, Susan, and Stefan Wager. “&lt;em&gt;Estimating treatment effects with causal forests: An application&lt;/em&gt;.” arXiv preprint arXiv:1902.07409 (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1902.07409&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Langer, Nishtha, Ram D. Gopal, and Ravi Bapna. “&lt;em&gt;Onward and Upward? An Empirical Investigation of Gender and Promotions in Information Technology Services&lt;/em&gt;.” Information Systems Research (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2019.0892&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zhang, Yingjie, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Personalized mobile targeting with user engagement stages: Combining a structural hidden markov model and field experiment&lt;/em&gt;.” Information Systems Research 30.3 (2019): 787-804. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2018.0831&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zhong, Ning, and David A. Schweidel. “&lt;em&gt;Capturing changes in social media content: a multiple latent changepoint topic model&lt;/em&gt;.” Marketing Science (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mksc.2019.1212&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bertsimas, Dimitris, and Nathan Kallus. “&lt;em&gt;From predictive to prescriptive analytics&lt;/em&gt;.” Management Science 66.3 (2020): 1025-1044. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2018.3253&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wang, Guihua, Jun Li, and Wallace J. Hopp. “&lt;em&gt;An instrumental variable tree approach for detecting heterogeneous treatment effects in observational studies.&lt;/em&gt;“ Ross School of Business Paper (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2021.4084?af=R&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Causality-and-Machine-Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Causality-and-Machine-Learning&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Causality and Machine Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Causality and Machine Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pearl, Judea. “&lt;em&gt;Causal inference in statistics: An overview.&lt;/em&gt;“ Statistics surveys 3 (2009): 96-146. &lt;a href=&#34;https://projecteuclid.org/journals/statistics-surveys/volume-3/issue-none/Causal-inference-in-statistics-An-overview/10.1214/09-SS057.full&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schölkopf, Bernhard. “&lt;em&gt;Causality for machine learning.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1911.10500 (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1911.10500&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guo, Ruocheng, et al. “&lt;em&gt;A survey of learning causality with data: Problems and methods.&lt;/em&gt;“ ACM Computing Surveys (CSUR) 53.4 (2020): 1-37. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3397269&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yao, Liuyi, et al. “&lt;em&gt;A survey on causal inference.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:2002.02770 (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2002.02770&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schnabel, Tobias, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Recommendations as treatments: Debiasing learning and evaluation.&lt;/em&gt;“ international conference on machine learning. PMLR, 2016. &lt;a href=&#34;http://proceedings.mlr.press/v48/schnabel16.html&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonner, Stephen, and Flavian Vasile. “&lt;em&gt;Causal embeddings for recommendation.&lt;/em&gt;“ Proceedings of the 12th ACM conference on recommender systems. 2018. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3240323.3240360&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wang, Yixin, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Causal Inference for Recommender Systems.&lt;/em&gt;“ Fourteenth ACM Conference on Recommender Systems. 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3383313.3412225&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chen, Jiawei, et al. “&lt;em&gt;AutoDebias: Learning to Debias for Recommendation.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:2105.04170 (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2105.04170&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;article class=&#34;message message-immersive is-primary&#34;&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fab fa-microsoft&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Microsoft Research hosts its causality research at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/research/group/causal-inference/&#34;&gt;Causality and Machine Learning&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;Digital-Beauty-Filter&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Digital-Beauty-Filter&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Digital Beauty Filter&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Digital Beauty Filter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/03/05/1020133/ai-algorithm-rate-beauty-score-attractive-face/&#34;&gt;I asked an AI to tell me how beautiful I am&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/04/02/1021635/beauty-filters-young-girls-augmented-reality-social-media/&#34;&gt;Beauty filters are changing the way young girls see themselves&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/06/10/1026074/tiktok-mandatory-beauty-filter-bug/&#34;&gt;TikTok changed the shape of some people’s faces without asking&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.technologyreview.com/2021/08/15/1031804/digital-beauty-filters-photoshop-photo-editing-colorism-racism/&#34;&gt;How digital beauty filters perpetuate colorism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Losh, Elizabeth. “&lt;em&gt;Selfies| Feminism Reads Big Data:” Social Physics,” Atomism, and Selfiecity.&lt;/em&gt;“ International Journal of Communication 9 (2015): 13. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ijoc.org/index.php/ijoc/article/view/3152&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Elias, Ana Sofia, and Rosalind Gill. “&lt;em&gt;Beauty surveillance: The digital self-monitoring cultures of neoliberalism.&lt;/em&gt;“ European Journal of Cultural Studies 21.1 (2018): 59-77. &lt;a href=&#34;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1177/1367549417705604&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Digital-Content-User-Generated-Content&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Digital-Content-User-Generated-Content&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Digital Content &amp;amp; User-Generated Content&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Digital Content &amp;amp; User-Generated Content&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ye, Hua, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Monetization of Digital Content: Drivers of Revenue on Q&amp;amp;a Platforms.&lt;/em&gt;“ Journal of Management Information Systems 38.2 (2021): 457-483. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/07421222.2021.1912934&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Gender&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Gender&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Gender&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Gender&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lin, Chen, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Do “Little Emperors” Get More Than “Little Empresses”? Boy-Girl Gender Discrimination as Evidenced by Consumption Behavior of Chinese Households.&lt;/em&gt;“ Marketing Science (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mksc.2021.1302?af=R&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Privacy&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Privacy&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Privacy&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Privacy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Godinho de Matos, Miguel, and Idris Adjerid. “&lt;em&gt;Consumer consent and firm targeting after GDPR: The case of a large telecom provider.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2021.4054?af=R&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Heng Xu, Nan Zhang (2022) From Contextualizing to Context Theorizing: Assessing Context Effects in Privacy Research. Management Science 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/mnsc.2021.4249&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Theory-of-Acceptance&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Theory-of-Acceptance&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Theory of Acceptance&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Theory of Acceptance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dwivedi, Yogesh K., et al. “A meta-analysis based modified unified theory of acceptance and use of technology (meta-UTAUT): a review of emerging literature.” Current opinion in psychology 36 (2020): 13-18. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1016/j.copsyc.2020.03.008&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blut, Markus, et al. “Meta-Analysis of the Unified Theory of Acceptance and Use of Technology (UTAUT): Challenging its Validity and Charting a Research Agenda in the Red Ocean,” Journal of the Association for Information Systems (2022), 23(1), 13-95. &lt;a href=&#34;https://aisel.aisnet.org/jais/vol23/iss1/10&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Fake-News-on-Social-Media&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Fake-News-on-Social-Media&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Fake News on Social Media&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Fake News on Social Media&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wang, Shuting, Min-Seok Pang, and Paul A. Pavlou. “Cure or Poison? Identity Verification and the Posting of Fake News on Social Media.” &lt;em&gt;Journal of Management Information Systems&lt;/em&gt; 38.4 (2021): 1011-1038. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/07421222.2021.1990615&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Horner, Christy Galletta, et al. “Emotions: The Unexplored Fuel of Fake News on Social Media.” &lt;em&gt;Journal of Management Information Systems&lt;/em&gt; 38.4 (2021): 1039-1066. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/07421222.2021.1990610&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deng, Bingjie, and Michael Chau. “The Effect of the Expressed Anger and Sadness on Online News Believability.” &lt;em&gt;Journal of Management Information Systems&lt;/em&gt; 38.4 (2021): 959-988. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/07421222.2021.1990607&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Turel, Ofir, and Babajide Osatuyi. “Biased Credibility and Sharing of Fake News on Social Media: Considering Peer Context and Self-Objectivity State.” &lt;em&gt;Journal of Management Information Systems&lt;/em&gt; 38.4 (2021): 931-958. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/07421222.2021.1990614&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ng, Ka Chung, Jie Tang, and Dongwon Lee. “The Effect of Platform Intervention Policies on Fake News Dissemination and Survival: An Empirical Examination.” &lt;em&gt;Journal of Management Information Systems&lt;/em&gt; 38.4 (2021): 898-930. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/07421222.2021.1990612&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;George, Jordana, Natalie Gerhart, and Russell Torres. “Uncovering the Truth about Fake News: A Research Model Grounded in Multi-Disciplinary Literature.” &lt;em&gt;Journal of Management Information Systems&lt;/em&gt; 38.4 (2021): 1067-1094. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/07421222.2021.1990608&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mohamed Mostagir, Asuman Ozdaglar, James Siderius (2022) When Is Society Susceptible to Manipulation?. Management Science 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/mnsc.2021.4265&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jackie London Jr., Siyuan Li, Heshan Sun (2022) Seems Legit: An Investigation of the Assessing and Sharing of Unverifiable Messages on Online Social Networks. Information Systems Research 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/isre.2021.1095&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Social-Media-Marketing&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Social-Media-Marketing&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Social Media Marketing&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Social Media Marketing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tingting Nian, Arun Sundararajan (2022) Social Media Marketing, Quality Signaling, and the Goldilocks Principle. Information Systems Research 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2021.1067?af=R&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jens Foerderer, Sebastian W. Schuetz (2022) Data Breach Announcements and Stock Market Reactions: A Matter of Timing?. Management Science 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/mnsc.2021.4264&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Online-Reviews&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Online-Reviews&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Online Reviews&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Online Reviews&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limin Fang (2022) The Effects of Online Review Platforms on Restaurant Revenue, Consumer Learning, and Welfare. Management Science 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/mnsc.2021.4279&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jinghui (Jove) Hou, Xiao Ma (2022) Space Norms for Constructing Quality Reviews on Online Consumer Review Sites. Information Systems Research 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/isre.2022.1102&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Gamification&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Gamification&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Gamification&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Gamification&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Behnaz Bojd, Xiaolong Song, Yong Tan, Xiangbin Yan (2022) Gamified Challenges in Online Weight-Loss Communities. Information Systems Research 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/isre.2021.1081&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Peer-Influence&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Peer-Influence&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Peer Influence&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Peer Influence&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jung, JaeHwuen, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Words Matter! Toward a Prosocial Call-to-Action for Online Referral: Evidence from Two Field Experiments.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2019.0873&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bryan Bollinger, Kenneth Gillingham, A. Justin Kirkpatrick, Steven Sexton (2022) Visibility and Peer Influence in Durable Good Adoption. Marketing Science 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/mksc.2021.1306&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Technical-Model-Design-Science&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Technical-Model-Design-Science&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Technical Model &amp;#x2F; Design Science&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Technical Model &amp;#x2F; Design Science&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Reinforcement-Learning-1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Reinforcement-Learning-1&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Reinforcement Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Reinforcement Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kaelbling, Leslie Pack, Michael L. Littman, and Andrew W. Moore. “&lt;em&gt;Reinforcement learning: A survey.&lt;/em&gt;“ Journal of artificial intelligence research 4 (1996): 237-285. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.jair.org/index.php/jair/article/view/10166&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arulkumaran, Kai, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Deep reinforcement learning: A brief survey.&lt;/em&gt;“ IEEE Signal Processing Magazine 34.6 (2017): 26-38. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/8103164&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Li, Yuxi. “&lt;em&gt;Deep reinforcement learning.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1810.06339 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1810.06339&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Li, Yuxi. “&lt;em&gt;Reinforcement learning applications.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1908.06973 (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1908.06973&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liebman, Elad, Maytal Saar-Tsechansky, and Peter Stone. “&lt;em&gt;The Right Music at the Right Time: Adaptive Personalized Playlists Based on Sequence Modeling.&lt;/em&gt;“ MIS Quarterly 43.3 (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://misq.org/the-right-music-at-the-right-time-adaptive-personalized-playlists-based-on-sequence-modeling.html&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wang, Hao-nan, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Deep reinforcement learning: a survey.&lt;/em&gt;“ Frontiers of Information Technology &amp;amp; Electronic Engineering (2020): 1-19. &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1631/FITEE.1900533&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parker-Holder, Jack, et al. “Automated Reinforcement Learning (AutoRL): A Survey and Open Problems.” &lt;em&gt;arXiv preprint arXiv:2201.03916&lt;/em&gt; (2022). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2201.03916&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Self-Supervised-Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Self-Supervised-Learning&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Self-Supervised Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Self-Supervised Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jing, Longlong, and Yingli Tian. “Self-supervised visual feature learning with deep neural networks: A survey.” &lt;em&gt;IEEE transactions on pattern analysis and machine intelligence&lt;/em&gt; 43.11 (2020): 4037-4058. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1109/TPAMI.2020.2992393&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Xie, Yaochen, et al. “Self-supervised learning of graph neural networks: A unified review.” &lt;em&gt;arXiv preprint arXiv:2102.10757&lt;/em&gt; (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2102.10757&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liu, Yixin, et al. “Graph self-supervised learning: A survey.” &lt;em&gt;arXiv preprint arXiv:2103.00111&lt;/em&gt; (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2103.00111&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jaiswal, Ashish, et al. “A survey on contrastive self-supervised learning.” &lt;em&gt;Technologies&lt;/em&gt; 9.1 (2021): 2. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.3390/technologies9010002&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liu, Xiao, et al. “Self-supervised learning: Generative or contrastive.” &lt;em&gt;IEEE Transactions on Knowledge and Data Engineering&lt;/em&gt; (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.ieeecomputersociety.org/10.1109/TKDE.2021.3090866&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Transfer-Learning-1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Transfer-Learning-1&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Transfer Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Transfer Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pan, Sinno Jialin, and Qiang Yang. “A survey on transfer learning.” &lt;em&gt;IEEE Transactions on knowledge and data engineering&lt;/em&gt; 22.10 (2009): 1345-1359. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1109/TKDE.2009.191&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weiss, Karl, Taghi M. Khoshgoftaar, and DingDing Wang. “A survey of transfer learning.” &lt;em&gt;Journal of Big data&lt;/em&gt; 3.1 (2016): 1-40. &lt;a href=&#34;https://journalofbigdata.springeropen.com/articles/10.1186/s40537-016-0043-6&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tan, Chuanqi, et al. “A survey on deep transfer learning.” &lt;em&gt;International conference on artificial neural networks&lt;/em&gt;. Springer, Cham, 2018. &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-030-01424-7_27&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zhuang, Fuzhen, et al. “A comprehensive survey on transfer learning.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the IEEE&lt;/em&gt; 109.1 (2020): 43-76. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1109/JPROC.2020.3004555&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Differential-Privacy&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Differential-Privacy&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Differential Privacy&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Differential Privacy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dwork, Cynthia, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Calibrating noise to sensitivity in private data analysis.&lt;/em&gt;“ Theory of cryptography conference. Springer, Berlin, Heidelberg, 2006. &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/11681878_14&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zheng, Qinqing, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Sharp Composition Bounds for Gaussian Differential Privacy via Edgeworth Expansion.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:2003.04493 (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1911.11607&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Goodfellow, Ian. “Efficient per-example gradient computations.” arXiv preprint arXiv:1510.01799 (2015). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1510.01799&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Abadi, Martin, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Deep learning with differential privacy.&lt;/em&gt;“ Proceedings of the 2016 ACM SIGSAC Conference on Computer and Communications Security. 2016. &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1607.00133&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mironov, Ilya. “&lt;em&gt;Rényi differential privacy.&lt;/em&gt;“ 2017 IEEE 30th Computer Security Foundations Symposium (CSF). IEEE, 2017. &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1702.07476&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;McMahan, H. Brendan, et al. “&lt;em&gt;A general approach to adding differential privacy to iterative training procedures.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1812.06210 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1812.06210&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mironov, Ilya, Kunal Talwar, and Li Zhang. “&lt;em&gt;Rényi  Differential Privacy of the Sampled Gaussian Mechanism.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1908.10530 (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1908.10530&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dwork, Cynthia, and Aaron Roth. “&lt;em&gt;The algorithmic foundations of differential privacy&lt;/em&gt;.” Foundations and Trends in Theoretical Computer Science 9.3-4 (2014): 211-407. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tau.ac.il/~saharon/BigData2015/privacybook.pdf&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dwork, Cynthia, and Adam Smith. “&lt;em&gt;Differential privacy for statistics: What we know and what we want to learn.&lt;/em&gt;“ Journal of Privacy and Confidentiality 1.2 (2010). &lt;a href=&#34;https://journalprivacyconfidentiality.org/index.php/jpc/article/view/570&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ji, Zhanglong, Zachary C. Lipton, and Charles Elkan. “&lt;em&gt;Differential privacy and machine learning: a survey and review&lt;/em&gt;.” arXiv preprint arXiv:1412.7584 (2014). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1412.7584&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jiang, Honglu, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Differential Privacy and Its Applications in Social Network Analysis: A Survey&lt;/em&gt;.” arXiv preprint arXiv:2010.02973 (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2010.02973&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yang, Mengmeng, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Local differential privacy and its applications: A comprehensive survey&lt;/em&gt;.” arXiv preprint arXiv:2008.03686 (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2008.03686&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Explainable-ML-DL-AI&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Explainable-ML-DL-AI&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Explainable ML &amp;#x2F; DL &amp;#x2F; AI&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Explainable ML &amp;#x2F; DL &amp;#x2F; AI&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arrieta, Alejandro Barredo, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Explainable Artificial Intelligence (XAI): Concepts, taxonomies, opportunities and challenges toward responsible AI.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Fusion 58 (2020): 82-115. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1566253519308103&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lipton, Zachary C. “&lt;em&gt;The mythos of model interpretability.&lt;/em&gt;“ Queue 16.3 (2018): 31-57. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/pdf/10.1145/3236386.3241340&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Angelino, Elaine, et al. “Learning certifiably optimal rule lists for categorical data.” &lt;em&gt;arXiv preprint arXiv:1704.01701&lt;/em&gt; (2017). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1704.01701#&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wang, Zhuo, et al. “Scalable Rule-Based Representation Learning for Interpretable Classification.” &lt;em&gt;arXiv preprint arXiv:2109.15103&lt;/em&gt; (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2109.15103&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Molnar, Christoph. &lt;em&gt;Interpretable machine learning&lt;/em&gt;. 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://christophm.github.io/interpretable-ml-book/&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Text-Summarization&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Text-Summarization&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Text Summarization&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Text Summarization&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rush, Alexander M., Sumit Chopra, and Jason Weston. “&lt;em&gt;A neural attention model for abstractive sentence summarization.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1509.00685 (2015). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1509.00685&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chen, Yen-Chun, and Mohit Bansal. “&lt;em&gt;Fast abstractive summarization with reinforce-selected sentence rewriting.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1805.11080 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1805.11080&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gehrmann, Sebastian, Yuntian Deng, and Alexander M. Rush. “&lt;em&gt;Bottom-up abstractive summarization.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1808.10792 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1808.10792&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Graph-Neural-Network&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Graph-Neural-Network&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Graph Neural Network&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Graph Neural Network&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kipf, T. N. “&lt;em&gt;Deep learning with graph-structured representations.&lt;/em&gt;“ (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://pure.uva.nl/ws/files/46900201/Thesis.pdf&#34;&gt;pdf&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wu, Zonghan, et al. “&lt;em&gt;A comprehensive survey on graph neural networks.&lt;/em&gt;“ IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/9046288?casa_token=CHO5GWiPHY8AAAAA:-h-OKzI47m0fMC0d9Vaj4PEDrSF2JaQ84sHP7_KJ7dw1Yd9EzAUKv_DUmBVg_JdRXR0xDEJcpjg&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zhou, Jie, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Graph neural networks: A review of methods and applications.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1812.08434 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1812.08434&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zhang, Chuxu, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Heterogeneous graph neural network.&lt;/em&gt;“ Proceedings of the 25th ACM SIGKDD International Conference on Knowledge Discovery &amp;amp; Data Mining. 2019. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3292500.3330961&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wang, Xiao, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Heterogeneous graph attention network.&lt;/em&gt;“ The World Wide Web Conference. 2019. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3308558.3313562&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hu, Ziniu, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Heterogeneous graph transformer.&lt;/em&gt;“ Proceedings of The Web Conference 2020. 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3366423.3380027&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Graph-Embedding&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Graph-Embedding&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Graph Embedding&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Graph Embedding&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Goyal, Palash, and Emilio Ferrara. “&lt;em&gt;Graph embedding techniques, applications, and performance: A survey.&lt;/em&gt;“ Knowledge-Based Systems 151 (2018): 78-94. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0950705118301540?casa_token=WgM1v1dCs0gAAAAA:z3R22qL6tLu8jVi85RQvyYrW9KMMFsh33Q_7msMwXeJxDZbU2j_G9rtuLW-B7Ntd8w11hbgdMyU&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Active-Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Active-Learning&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Active Learning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Active Learning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aggarwal, C. C., Kong, X., Gu, Q., Han, J., &amp;amp; Yu, P. S. (2014). “&lt;em&gt;Active learning: A survey&lt;/em&gt;“. In Data Classification: Algorithms and Applications (pp. 571-605). CRC Press. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1201/b17320&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ren, Pengzhen, et al. “&lt;em&gt;A Survey of Deep Active Learning.&lt;/em&gt;“ ArXiv:2009.00236 [Cs, Stat], Aug. 2020. arXiv.org. &lt;a href=&#34;http://arxiv.org/abs/2009.00236&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atahan, Pelin, and Sumit Sarkar. “&lt;em&gt;Accelerated learning of user profiles.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science 57.2 (2011): 215-239. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.1100.1266&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Label-Noise&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Label-Noise&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Label Noise&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Label Noise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Han, Bo, et al. “A survey of label-noise representation learning: Past, present and future.” arXiv preprint arXiv:2011.04406 (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2011.04406&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Graphical-Causality&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Graphical-Causality&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Graphical Causality&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Graphical Causality&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bernhard Schölkopf, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Towards Causal Representation Learning&lt;/em&gt;.” (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2102.11107&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Recommendation-Systems-1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Recommendation-Systems-1&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Recommendation Systems&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Recommendation Systems&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kunaver, Matevž, and Tomaž Požrl. “Diversity in recommender systems–A survey.” &lt;em&gt;Knowledge-based systems&lt;/em&gt; 123 (2017): 154-162. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0950705117300680&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kaminskas, Marius, and Derek Bridge. “Diversity, serendipity, novelty, and coverage: a survey and empirical analysis of beyond-accuracy objectives in recommender systems.” &lt;em&gt;ACM Transactions on Interactive Intelligent Systems (TiiS)&lt;/em&gt; 7.1 (2016): 1-42. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/2926720&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wu, Qiong, et al. “Recent advances in diversified recommendation.” &lt;em&gt;arXiv preprint arXiv:1905.06589&lt;/em&gt; (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1905.06589&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anelli, Vito Walter, et al. “Elliot: a comprehensive and rigorous framework for reproducible recommender systems evaluation.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the 44th International ACM SIGIR Conference on Research and Development in Information Retrieval&lt;/em&gt;. 2021. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1145/3404835.3463245&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sisinflab/elliot&#34;&gt;code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Si, Zihua et al. “A Model-Agnostic Causal Learning Framework for Recommendation using Search Data.” (2022). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2202.04514&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/Ethan00Si/Instrumental-variables-for-recommendation&#34;&gt;code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;Attacking-Recommendation-Systems&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Attacking-Recommendation-Systems&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Attacking Recommendation Systems&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Attacking Recommendation Systems&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Su, Xue-Feng, Hua-Jun Zeng, and Zheng Chen. “Finding group shilling in recommendation system.” &lt;em&gt;Special interest tracks and posters of the 14th international conference on World Wide Web&lt;/em&gt;. 2005. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/1062745.1062818&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;O’Donovan, John, and Barry Smyth. “Is trust robust? An analysis of trust-based recommendation.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the 11th international conference on Intelligent user interfaces&lt;/em&gt;. 2006. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/1111449.1111476&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hurley, Neil J., Michael P. O’Mahony, and Guenole CM Silvestre. “Attacking recommender systems: A cost-benefit analysis.” &lt;em&gt;IEEE Intelligent Systems&lt;/em&gt; 22.3 (2007): 64-68. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/4216982&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Patel, Krupa, et al. “A state of art survey on shilling attack in collaborative filtering based recommendation system.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of First International Conference on Information and Communication Technology for Intelligent Systems: Volume 1&lt;/em&gt;. Springer, Cham, 2016. &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-319-30933-0_38&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fang, Minghong, et al. “Poisoning attacks to graph-based recommender systems.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the 34th Annual Computer Security Applications Conference&lt;/em&gt;. 2018. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3274694.3274706&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hu, Rui, et al. “Targeted poisoning attacks on social recommender systems.” &lt;em&gt;2019 IEEE Global Communications Conference (GLOBECOM)&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE, 2019. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/9013539&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zhang, Hengtong, et al. “Practical data poisoning attack against next-item recommendation.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of The Web Conference 2020&lt;/em&gt;. 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3366423.3379992&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Song, Junshuai, et al. “Poisonrec: an adaptive data poisoning framework for attacking black-box recommender systems.” &lt;em&gt;2020 IEEE 36th International Conference on Data Engineering (ICDE)&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE, 2020. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/9101655&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wu, Zih-Wun, Chiao-Ting Chen, and Szu-Hao Huang. “Poisoning attacks against knowledge graph-based recommendation systems using deep reinforcement learning.” &lt;em&gt;Neural Computing and Applications&lt;/em&gt; (2021): 1-19. &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00521-021-06573-8&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chen, Liang, et al. “Data poisoning attacks on neighborhood‐based recommender systems.” &lt;em&gt;Transactions on Emerging Telecommunications Technologies&lt;/em&gt; 32.6 (2021): e3872. &lt;a href=&#34;https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/ett.3872&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Zhang, Hengtong, et al. “Data Poisoning Attack against Recommender System Using Incomplete and Perturbed Data.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the 27th ACM SIGKDD Conference on Knowledge Discovery &amp;amp; Data Mining&lt;/em&gt;. 2021. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3447548.3467233&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fan, Wenqi, et al. “Attacking Black-box Recommendations via Copying Cross-domain User Profiles.” &lt;em&gt;2021 IEEE 37th International Conference on Data Engineering (ICDE)&lt;/em&gt;. IEEE, 2021. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/9458627&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;User-Item-Matrix-Factorization&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#User-Item-Matrix-Factorization&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;User-Item Matrix Factorization&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;User-Item Matrix Factorization&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Han, Soyeon Caren, et al. “GLocal-K: Global and Local Kernels for Recommender Systems.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the 30th ACM International Conference on Information &amp;amp; Knowledge Management&lt;/em&gt;. 2021. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1145/3459637.3482112&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;Debias&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Debias&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Debias&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Debias&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schnabel, Tobias, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Recommendations as treatments: Debiasing learning and evaluation.&lt;/em&gt;“ international conference on machine learning. PMLR, 2016. &lt;a href=&#34;http://proceedings.mlr.press/v48/schnabel16.html&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chen, Jiawei, et al. “&lt;em&gt;AutoDebias: Learning to Debias for Recommendation.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:2105.04170 (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2105.04170&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fab fa-github&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://jiawei-chen.github.io/&#34;&gt;Jiawei Chen&lt;/a&gt; on github.com provides a repository at &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/jiawei-chen/RecDebiasing&#34;&gt;jiawei-chen/RecDebiasing&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;Lagrangian-Relaxation&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Lagrangian-Relaxation&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Lagrangian Relaxation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Lagrangian Relaxation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fisher, Marshall L. “&lt;em&gt;The Lagrangian relaxation method for solving integer programming problems.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management science 27.1 (1981): 1-18. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.27.1.1&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghoshal, Abhijeet, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Hiding Sensitive Information when Sharing Distributed Transactional Data.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information systems research 31.2 (2020): 473-490. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2019.0898&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Column-Generation&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Column-Generation&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Column Generation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Column Generation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Menon, Syam, and Sumit Sarkar. “&lt;em&gt;Privacy and Big Data: Scalable Approaches to Sanitize Large Transactional Databases for Sharing.&lt;/em&gt;“ MIS Quarterly 40.4 (2016). &lt;a href=&#34;https://misq.org/privacy-and-big-data-scalable-approaches-to-sanitize-large-transactional-databases-for-sharing.html&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dash, Sanjeeb, Oktay Günlük, and Dennis Wei. “&lt;em&gt;Boolean decision rules via column generation.&lt;/em&gt;“ arXiv preprint arXiv:1805.09901 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1805.09901&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Decision-Under-Uncertainty&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Decision-Under-Uncertainty&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Decision Under Uncertainty&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Decision Under Uncertainty&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sen, Suvrajeet, and Julia L. Higle. “&lt;em&gt;An introductory tutorial on stochastic linear programming models.&lt;/em&gt;“ Interfaces 29.2 (1999): 33-61. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/inte.29.2.33&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Probabilistic-Reasoning&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Probabilistic-Reasoning&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Probabilistic Reasoning&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Probabilistic Reasoning&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Li, Zhepeng, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Utility-based link recommendation for online social networks.&lt;/em&gt;“ Management Science 63.6 (2017): 1938-1952. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/mnsc.2016.2446&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ghoshal, Abhijeet, Syam Menon, and Sumit Sarkar. “&lt;em&gt;Recommendations using information from multiple association rules: A probabilistic approach.&lt;/em&gt;“ Information Systems Research 26.3 (2015): 532-551. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pubsonline.informs.org/doi/abs/10.1287/isre.2015.0583&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Agent-based-Modeling-Simulation&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Agent-based-Modeling-Simulation&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Agent-based Modeling &amp;amp; Simulation&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Agent-based Modeling &amp;amp; Simulation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bonabeau, Eric. “&lt;em&gt;Agent-based modeling: Methods and techniques for simulating human systems.&lt;/em&gt;“ Proceedings of the national academy of sciences 99.suppl 3 (2002): 7280-7287. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pnas.org/content/99/suppl_3/7280&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Macal, Charles M., and Michael J. North. “&lt;em&gt;Tutorial on agent-based modeling and simulation&lt;/em&gt;.” Proceedings of the Winter Simulation Conference, 2005.. IEEE, 2005. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/1574234&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Railsback, Steven F., Steven L. Lytinen, and Stephen K. Jackson. “&lt;em&gt;Agent-based simulation platforms: Review and development recommendations.&lt;/em&gt;“ Simulation 82.9 (2006): 609-623. &lt;a href=&#34;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0037549706073695&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An, Li. “&lt;em&gt;Modeling human decisions in coupled human and natural systems: Review of agent-based models&lt;/em&gt;.” Ecological Modelling 229 (2012): 25-36. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0304380011003802&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Abar, Sameera, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Agent Based Modelling and Simulation tools: A review of the state-of-art software.&lt;/em&gt;“ Computer Science Review 24 (2017): 13-33. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1574013716301198&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mladenov, Martin, et al. “RecSim NG: Toward Principled Uncertainty Modeling for Recommender Ecosystems.” &lt;em&gt;arXiv preprint arXiv:2103.08057&lt;/em&gt; (2021). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/2103.08057&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://ai.googleblog.com/2021/04/flexible-scalable-differentiable.html&#34;&gt;official webiste&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/google-research/recsim_ng&#34;&gt;github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Influence-Maximization&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Influence-Maximization&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Influence Maximization&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Influence Maximization&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Li, Yuchen, et al. “Influence maximization on social graphs: A survey.” IEEE Transactions on Knowledge and Data Engineering 30.10 (2018): 1852-1872. &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/8295265&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Banerjee, Suman, Mamata Jenamani, and Dilip Kumar Pratihar. “A survey on influence maximization in a social network.” Knowledge and Information Systems 62.9 (2020): 3417-3455. &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1808.05502&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;De Nittis, Giuseppe, and Nicola Gatti. “How to maximize the spread of social influence: A survey.” arXiv preprint arXiv:1806.07757 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://arxiv.org/abs/1806.07757&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Video-Content-Structuring&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Video-Content-Structuring&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Video Content Structuring&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Video Content Structuring&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;article class=&#34;message message-immersive is-primary&#34;&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fas fa-book&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; Scholarpedia provides a Wikipedia page at &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.scholarpedia.org/article/Video_Content_Structuring&#34;&gt;Video Content Structuring - Scholarpedia&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;Topic-Modeling&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Topic-Modeling&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Topic Modeling&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Topic Modeling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jelodar, Hamed, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Latent Dirichlet allocation (LDA) and topic modeling: models, applications, a survey.&lt;/em&gt;“ &lt;em&gt;Multimedia Tools and Applications&lt;/em&gt; 78.11 (2019): 15169-15211. &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11042-018-6894-4&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qiang, Jipeng, et al. “&lt;em&gt;Short text topic modeling techniques, applications, and performance: a survey.&lt;/em&gt;“ &lt;em&gt;IEEE Transactions on Knowledge and Data Engineering&lt;/em&gt; (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;https://ieeexplore.ieee.org/abstract/document/9086136&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vayansky, Ike, and Sathish AP Kumar. “&lt;em&gt;A review of topic modeling methods.&lt;/em&gt;“ &lt;em&gt;Information Systems&lt;/em&gt; 94 (2020): 101582. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0306437920300703&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kherwa, Pooja, and Poonam Bansal. “&lt;em&gt;Topic modeling: a comprehensive review.&lt;/em&gt;“ &lt;em&gt;EAI Endorsed transactions on scalable information systems&lt;/em&gt; 7.24 (2020). &lt;a href=&#34;http://eprints.eudl.eu/id/eprint/682/&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chauhan, Uttam, and Apurva Shah. “&lt;em&gt;Topic Modeling Using Latent Dirichlet allocation: A Survey.&lt;/em&gt;“ &lt;em&gt;ACM Computing Surveys (CSUR)&lt;/em&gt; 54.7 (2021): 1-35. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3462478&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Team&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Team&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Team&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Team&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Devine, Dennis J., and Jennifer L. Philips. “Do smarter teams do better: A meta-analysis of cognitive ability and team performance.” &lt;em&gt;Small group research&lt;/em&gt; 32.5 (2001): 507-532. &lt;a href=&#34;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/104649640103200501&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kozlowski, Steve WJ, and Daniel R. Ilgen. “Enhancing the effectiveness of work groups and teams.” &lt;em&gt;Psychological science in the public interest&lt;/em&gt; 7.3 (2006): 77-124. &lt;a href=&#34;https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/full/10.1111/j.1529-1006.2006.00030.x&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wang, Xinyu, Zhou Zhao, and Wilfred Ng. “A comparative study of team formation in social networks.” &lt;em&gt;International conference on database systems for advanced applications&lt;/em&gt;. Springer, Cham, 2015. &lt;a href=&#34;https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-319-18120-2_23&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Andrejczuk, Ewa, et al. “The composition and formation of effective teams: computer science meets organizational psychology.” &lt;em&gt;The Knowledge Engineering Review&lt;/em&gt; 33 (2018). &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/knowledge-engineering-review/article/abs/composition-and-formation-of-effective-teams-computer-science-meets-organizational-psychology/79DBFF072E6FD82E5AF1FE1705E57C2C&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gómez-Zará, Diego, Leslie A. DeChurch, and Noshir S. Contractor. “A taxonomy of team-assembly systems: Understanding how people use technologies to form teams.” &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the ACM on Human-Computer Interaction&lt;/em&gt; 4.CSCW2 (2020): 1-36. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3415252&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Juárez, Julio, Cipriano Santos, and Carlos A. Brizuela. “A Comprehensive Review and a Taxonomy Proposal of Team Formation Problems.” &lt;em&gt;ACM Computing Surveys (CSUR)&lt;/em&gt; 54.7 (2021): 1-33. &lt;a href=&#34;https://dl.acm.org/doi/abs/10.1145/3465399&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Mobile-User-Behavior&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Mobile-User-Behavior&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Mobile User Behavior&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Mobile User Behavior&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shaohui Wu, Yong Tan, Yubo Chen, Yitian (Sky) Liang (2022) How Is Mobile User Behavior Different?—A Hidden Markov Model of Cross-Mobile Application Usage Dynamics. Information Systems Research 0(0) &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/isre.2021.1093&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Dynamic-Pricing&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Dynamic-Pricing&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Dynamic Pricing&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Dynamic Pricing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;N. Bora Keskin, Yuexing Li, Jing-Sheng Song (2022) Data-Driven Dynamic Pricing and Ordering with Perishable Inventory in a Changing Environment. Management Science 0(0). &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1287/mnsc.2021.4011&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Reliable-Prediction&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Reliable-Prediction&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Reliable Prediction&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Reliable Prediction&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Romano, Yaniv, Evan Patterson, and Emmanuel Candes. “Conformalized quantile regression.” &lt;em&gt;Advances in neural information processing systems&lt;/em&gt; 32 (2019). &lt;a href=&#34;https://proceedings.neurips.cc/paper/2019/hash/5103c3584b063c431bd1268e9b5e76fb-Abstract.html&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/yromano/cqr&#34;&gt;code&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sesia, Matteo, and Emmanuel J. Candès. “A comparison of some conformal quantile regression methods.” Stat 9.1 (2020): e261. &lt;a href=&#34;https://doi.org/10.1002/sta4.261&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;article class=&#34;message message-immersive is-primary&#34;&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;message-body&#34;&gt;
&lt;i class=&#34;fab fa-github&#34;&gt;&lt;/i&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/datawhalechina/easy-rl&#34;&gt;Model Agnostic Prediction Interval Estimator (MAPIE)&lt;/a&gt; is a python toolkit for prediction interval estimation.
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/article&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a style=&#34;background-color:black;color:white;text-decoration:none;padding:4px 6px;font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &amp;quot;San Francisco&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Ubuntu, Roboto, Noto, &amp;quot;Segoe UI&amp;quot;, Arial, sans-serif;font-size:12px;font-weight:bold;line-height:1.2;display:inline-block;border-radius:3px&#34; href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/@syinq?utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=photographer-credit&amp;amp;utm_content=creditBadge&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; title=&#34;Download free do whatever you want high-resolution photos from Susan Yin&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;&lt;svg xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; style=&#34;height:12px;width:auto;position:relative;vertical-align:middle;top:-2px;fill:white&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 32 32&#34;&gt;&lt;title&gt;unsplash-logo&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M10 9V0h12v9H10zm12 5h10v18H0V14h10v9h12v-9z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;thumbnail by Susan Yin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/04/21/Draw-Beautifully-in-Latex-Resources-of-TikZ/</guid>
            <title>Draw Beautifully in Latex - Resources of PGF/TikZ</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/04/21/Draw-Beautifully-in-Latex-Resources-of-TikZ/</link>
            <category>Ph.D.</category>
            <category>Writing</category>
            <category>Latex</category>
            <category>Packages</category>
            <category>PGF/TikZ</category>
            <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2020 19:42:34 -0500</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PGF&amp;#x2F;Ti&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;Z&lt;/strong&gt; is a pair of languages for producing vector graphics (e.g., technical illustrations and drawings) from a geometric&amp;#x2F;algebraic description, with standard features including the drawing of points, lines, arrows, paths, circles, ellipses and polygons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;footer&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;cite&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/PGF/TikZ&#34;&gt;PGF/TikZ - Wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post incldues resources of PGF&amp;#x2F;Ti&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;Z for references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;PGF-TikZ-Official-Manual&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#PGF-TikZ-Official-Manual&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;PGF&amp;#x2F;TikZ Official Manual&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;PGF&amp;#x2F;Ti&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;Z Official Manual&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://mirrors.ctan.org/graphics/pgf/base/doc/pgfmanual.pdf&#34;&gt;PGF&amp;#x2F;Ti&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;Z Official Manual&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;PGF-TikZ-Books&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#PGF-TikZ-Books&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;PGF&amp;#x2F;TikZ Books&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;PGF&amp;#x2F;Ti&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;Z Books&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.google.com/books/edition/_/t3ZZDwAAQBAJ?hl=en&amp;gbpv=0&#34;&gt;Ti&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;Z Cookbook for Diagram in Economics with Step-by-Step Illustration, By Chiu Yu Ko&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;PGF-TikZ-Examples&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#PGF-TikZ-Examples&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;PGF&amp;#x2F;TikZ Examples&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;PGF&amp;#x2F;Ti&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;Z Examples&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://texample.net/tikz/examples/&#34;&gt;Examples from texample.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sites.google.com/site/kochiuyu/Tikz&#34;&gt;Ti&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;Z Online Tutorial (old version), by Chiu Yui Ko&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://kochiuyu.github.io/tikz/&#34;&gt;Ti&lt;em&gt;k&lt;/em&gt;Z Online Tutorial (latest version), by Chiu Yui Ko&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a style=&#34;background-color:black;color:white;text-decoration:none;padding:4px 6px;font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &amp;quot;San Francisco&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Ubuntu, Roboto, Noto, &amp;quot;Segoe UI&amp;quot;, Arial, sans-serif;font-size:12px;font-weight:bold;line-height:1.2;display:inline-block;border-radius:3px&#34; href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/@kellysikkema?utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=photographer-credit&amp;amp;utm_content=creditBadge&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; title=&#34;Download free do whatever you want high-resolution photos from Kelly Sikkema&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;&lt;svg xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; style=&#34;height:12px;width:auto;position:relative;vertical-align:middle;top:-2px;fill:white&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 32 32&#34;&gt;&lt;title&gt;unsplash-logo&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M10 9V0h12v9H10zm12 5h10v18H0V14h10v9h12v-9z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;thumbnail by Kelly Sikkema&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/03/30/ITSS3300-SQL-Resources-2020-Spring/</guid>
            <title>ITSS3300 SQL Resources - 2020 Spring</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/03/30/ITSS3300-SQL-Resources-2020-Spring/</link>
            <category>JSOM</category>
            <category>Ph.D.</category>
            <category>Notes</category>
            <category>SQL</category>
            <category>ITSS3300</category>
            <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2020 15:47:19 -0500</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;Welcome! This post includes my video tutorial of hands-on SQL on Oracle Live SQL for &lt;a href=&#34;https://coursebook.utdallas.edu/ITSS3300/&#34;&gt;ITSS3300 - 2020 Spring&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;video-container&#34;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/J9ubNDHLD6Q&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; loading=&#34;lazy&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ntZ9A0bThwmZTMzBzGYgKyrGYICDkgSW/preview&#34;&gt;pdf&lt;/a&gt; and following codes come from the slides and sample script I used in class.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&#34;highlight sql&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span&gt;SQL Example Codes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;gutter&#34;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;2&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;4&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;5&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;6&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;7&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;8&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;9&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;11&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;12&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;13&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;14&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;15&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;16&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;17&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;18&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;19&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;20&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;21&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;22&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;23&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;24&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;25&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;26&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;27&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;28&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;29&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;30&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;31&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;32&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;33&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;34&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;35&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;36&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;37&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;38&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;39&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;40&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;41&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;42&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;43&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;44&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;45&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;46&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;47&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;48&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;49&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;51&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;52&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;53&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;54&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;55&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;56&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;57&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;58&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;59&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;60&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;61&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;62&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;63&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;64&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;65&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;66&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;67&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;68&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;69&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;70&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;71&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;72&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;73&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;74&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;75&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;76&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;77&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;78&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;79&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;80&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;81&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;82&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;83&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;84&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;85&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;86&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;87&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;88&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;89&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;90&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;91&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;92&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;93&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;94&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;95&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;96&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;97&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;98&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;99&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;100&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;101&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;102&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;103&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;104&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;105&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;106&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;107&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;108&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;109&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;110&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;111&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;112&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;code&#34;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: How To Comment */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Multi line comment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;   This is the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;   first SQL statement exmaple */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; PROD_ID, PROD_CATEGORY, PROD_SUB_CATEGORY &lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;-- Single line comment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; PRODUCT;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: How To Create Table*/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;CREATE&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;TABLE&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;Order_ID NUMBER(&lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;5&lt;/span&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;Order_Date &lt;span class=&#34;type&#34;&gt;DATE&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;Order_Priority VARCHAR2(&lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;20&lt;/span&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;Ord_Id VARCHAR2(&lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;10&lt;/span&gt;) );&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: How to Create Table with Constraint */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;CREATE&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;TABLE&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;Order_ID NUMBER(&lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;5&lt;/span&gt;) &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;PRIMARY&lt;/span&gt; KEY &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;NOT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;NULL&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;Order_Date &lt;span class=&#34;type&#34;&gt;DATE&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;Order_Priority VARCHAR2(&lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;20&lt;/span&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;Ord_Id VARCHAR2(&lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;10&lt;/span&gt;) );&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/*Example: How To Drop Table*/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;DROP&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;TABLE&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: INSERT INTO */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;INSERT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;INTO&lt;/span&gt; PRODUCT (Prod_id, Prod_Category, Prod_Sub_Category)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;VALUES&lt;/span&gt; (&lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_1&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;OFFICE SUPPLIES&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;STORAGE &amp;amp; ORGANIZATION&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;INSERT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;INTO&lt;/span&gt; PRODUCT (Prod_id, Prod_Sub_Category, Prod_Category)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;VALUES&lt;/span&gt; (&lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_1&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;STORAGE &amp;amp; ORGANIZATION&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;OFFICE SUPPLIES&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;INSERT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;INTO&lt;/span&gt; PRODUCT &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;VALUES&lt;/span&gt; (&lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_1&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;OFFICE SUPPLIES&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;STORAGE &amp;amp; ORGANIZATION&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: UPDATE */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;UPDATE&lt;/span&gt; PRODUCT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SET&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Sub_Category &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;FURNITURE &amp;amp; LIGHTING&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; Prod_id &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_1&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* What if no WHERE? */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;UPDATE&lt;/span&gt; PRODUCT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SET&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Sub_Category &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;FURNITURE &amp;amp; LIGHTING&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: SELECT Prod_id FROM PRODUCT*/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; Prod_id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; PRODUCT;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Select all columns from PRODUCT*/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; PRODUCT;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/*Example: Rename Sales as New_Sales*/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; Mkt_Id, &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;1.5&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt; Sales&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; Mkt_Id, &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;1.5&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt; Sales New_Sales&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/*Example: SELECT + FROM + WHERE + Logic Condition*/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_1&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;AND&lt;/span&gt; Order_Quantity &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;30&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_1&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;OR&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_10&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;NOT&lt;/span&gt; (Prod_Id &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_1&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;); &lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;-- Equivalent &amp;lt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/*Example: Get min and max of sales, average order quantity and number of records for Prod_1*/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;MIN&lt;/span&gt;(Sales) Min_Sales, &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;MAX&lt;/span&gt;(Sales) Max_Sales, &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;AVG&lt;/span&gt;(Order_Quantity) Avg_Ord_Q, &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;COUNT&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_1&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: ORDER BY Sales */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;Prod_1&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;AND&lt;/span&gt; Order_Quantity &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;ORDER&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;BY&lt;/span&gt; Sales &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;DESC&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/*Example: Get Prod_Id and their corresponding number and average profit. Order records by average profit descendingly */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id, &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;COUNT&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;), &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;AVG&lt;/span&gt;(Profit) AVG_Profit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; Order_Quantity &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;GROUP&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;BY&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;ORDER&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;BY&lt;/span&gt; AVG_Profit &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;DESC&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: HAVING */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id, &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;COUNT&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;), &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;AVG&lt;/span&gt;(Profit) AVG_Profit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; Order_Quantity &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;GROUP&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;BY&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;HAVING&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;COUNT&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;) &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;5&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;OR&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;AVG&lt;/span&gt;(Profit) &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;ORDER&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;BY&lt;/span&gt; AVG_Profit &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;DESC&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: HAVING */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id, &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;AVG&lt;/span&gt;(Profit) AVG_Profit&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; MARKET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; Order_Quantity &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;GROUP&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;BY&lt;/span&gt; Prod_Id&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;HAVING&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;COUNT&lt;/span&gt;(&lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;) &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;5&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;OR&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;built_in&#34;&gt;AVG&lt;/span&gt;(Profit) &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;number&#34;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;ORDER&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;BY&lt;/span&gt; AVG_Profit &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;DESC&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: JOIN */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS.Order_ID, ORDERS.Order_Priority, SHIPPING.Ship_Mode&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;JOIN&lt;/span&gt; SHIPPING &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;ON&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS.Order_ID &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; SHIPPING.Order_ID&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS.Order_Priority &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;string&#34;&gt;&amp;#x27;LOW&amp;#x27;&lt;/span&gt;; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: Query two tables via JOIN */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS.Order_ID, ORDERS.Order_Priority, SHIPPING.Ship_Mode&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;JOIN&lt;/span&gt; SHIPPING &lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;ON&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS.Order_ID &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; SHIPPING.Order_ID;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;comment&#34;&gt;/* Example: Query two tables via = syntax */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;SELECT&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS.Order_ID, ORDERS.Order_Priority, SHIPPING.Ship_Mode&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;FROM&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS, SHIPPING&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;keyword&#34;&gt;WHERE&lt;/span&gt; ORDERS.Order_ID &lt;span class=&#34;operator&#34;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; SHIPPING.Order_ID;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you also can download the slides and sample script from &lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/15oEs93pbIRQbB0qXPP3TNgqtY5M8Gd4O?usp=sharing&#34; title=&#34;SQL Slides and sample script&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What’s more, here are some learning resources for your reference:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Books&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Date, C. J. An Introduction to Database Systems (8th edition).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ullman, J. D. (2007). A first Course in Database Systems. Pearson Education India.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beaulieu, A. (2009). Learning SQL: Master SQL Fundamentals. O’Reilly Media, Inc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Online Website&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.tutorialspoint.com/sql/&#34;&gt;SQL in tutorialspoint.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.w3schools.com/sql/default.asp&#34;&gt;w3school SQL Tutorial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sqlzoo.net/&#34;&gt;SQLZOO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sqlbolt.com/&#34;&gt;SQLBolt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Video Courses&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.khanacademy.org/computing/computer-programming/sql&#34;&gt;Khan Academy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a style=&#34;background-color:black;color:white;text-decoration:none;padding:4px 6px;font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &amp;quot;San Francisco&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Ubuntu, Roboto, Noto, &amp;quot;Segoe UI&amp;quot;, Arial, sans-serif;font-size:12px;font-weight:bold;line-height:1.2;display:inline-block;border-radius:3px&#34; href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/@tvick?utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=photographer-credit&amp;amp;utm_content=creditBadge&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; title=&#34;Download free do whatever you want high-resolution photos from Taylor Vick&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;&lt;svg xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; style=&#34;height:12px;width:auto;position:relative;vertical-align:middle;top:-2px;fill:white&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 32 32&#34;&gt;&lt;title&gt;unsplash-logo&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M10 9V0h12v9H10zm12 5h10v18H0V14h10v9h12v-9z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;thumbnail by Taylor Vick&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/02/23/Notes-for-PhD-Job-Interview-Experiences-02-21-2020/</guid>
            <title>Notes for Ph.D. Job Interview Experiences 02-21-2020</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2020/02/23/Notes-for-PhD-Job-Interview-Experiences-02-21-2020/</link>
            <category>JSOM</category>
            <category>Ph.D.</category>
            <category>Notes</category>
            <category>Job</category>
            <category>Interview Experiences</category>
            <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 00:31:32 -0600</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;Are you a budding academic embarking on the journey to secure a tenure-track position in your field? The path can be challenging, but learning from the experiences of those who have successfully navigated it can be immensely helpful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a brief summary of insights and advice shared by three scholars, Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://leilahosseini.wixsite.com/leila&#34;&gt;Leila Hosseini&lt;/a&gt;, Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://sameermehta.me/&#34;&gt;Sameer Mehta&lt;/a&gt;, Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://muratmtunc.github.io/&#34;&gt;Murat Tunc&lt;/a&gt; during a panel discussion at the JSOM IS Seminar in 2020. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really appreciate the generous and comprehensive sharing about their job seeking experiences.&lt;br&gt;I also want to thank Dr. &lt;a href=&#34;https://jindal.utdallas.edu/faculty/varghese-jacob&#34;&gt;Varghese S. Jacob&lt;/a&gt; to host this panel.&lt;br&gt;These seasoned professionals offer invaluable guidance to aspiring tenure-track job seekers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Before-the-Interviews-Preparing-for-the-Position&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Before-the-Interviews-Preparing-for-the-Position&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Before the Interviews: Preparing for the Position&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Before the Interviews: Preparing for the Position&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The journey begins between July and October when academic institutions typically start posting tenure-track positions. The exact timing may vary depending on your field, so stay vigilant. It’s essential to have your application materials ready before the hiring season kicks off. These materials typically include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curriculum Vitae&lt;/strong&gt; (CV): A well-organized document highlighting your academic journey and achievements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teaching and Research Statements&lt;/strong&gt;: Clear and concise statements outlining your teaching philosophy and research interests.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teaching Evaluations&lt;/strong&gt;: Evidence of your teaching effectiveness, if available.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommendation Letters&lt;/strong&gt;: Strong letters of recommendation from reputable sources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paper Copies&lt;/strong&gt;: Copies of your publications or research papers (requirements may vary by institution).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity, Equity, and Inclusion (DEI) Statement&lt;/strong&gt;: Outlines of your commitment to promoting diversity, equity, and inclusion in academia.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember, only include projects and papers that you’re well-versed in. Additionally, be prepared to succinctly discuss the content of your CV within two minutes. Collaborating with your PhD colleagues can also be beneficial in this preparation phase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Interview-I-The-Initial-Encounter&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Interview-I-The-Initial-Encounter&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Interview I: The Initial Encounter&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Interview I: The Initial Encounter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first-round interview, whether conducted online or in person at a conference, usually lasts around 30 minutes. This interview typically follows a structured format:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introduce Yourself&lt;/strong&gt;: Begin by succinctly presenting your research focus and its relevance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research Landscape&lt;/strong&gt;: Discuss your research topics and methodologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research Details&lt;/strong&gt;: Articulate why your research is significant and provide specific insights into your work.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Research Questions&lt;/strong&gt;: Be prepared for philosophical inquiries about the Information Systems (IS) field. Share your future research plans, including topics, domains, and methodologies. Familiarize yourself with the faculty members you’d like to work with (at least two).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teaching Questions&lt;/strong&gt;: Expect questions about your teaching experience, teaching philosophy, and your plans for specific courses.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ask Your Questions&lt;/strong&gt;: Use this opportunity to inquire about the timeline for decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When managing your time during this interview, allocate approximately 90% to research-related topics, 5% to teaching, and 5% to your questions for the interviewers. Use your limited time to convey the key points of your research convincingly and demonstrate why you’re the right fit for the position.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to establish connections between your teaching and research. Articulate clear motivations for your choice of teaching domain rather than merely discussing a topic. Avoid making unsupported statements; always provide reasons and justifications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’re attending a conference, it’s not only an opportunity to network and make connections but also to prepare your application package. You might find universities actively hiring at these events, so having your materials on hand is crucial.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For international institutions, be ready to explain your motivation for seeking a position there clearly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Interview-II-The-Campus-Visit&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Interview-II-The-Campus-Visit&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Interview II: The Campus Visit&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Interview II: The Campus Visit&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Typically, you’ll receive campus visit invitations after the first-round interviews. Some schools may offer direct invitations without the initial interview, although this is less common. During your campus visit:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dress professionally, adhering to a business suit dress code, especially in a business school setting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remember, they’re not just looking for a researcher; they want an engaging colleague. Don’t immediately dive into your research; make it exciting and memorable. Incorporate anecdotes, jokes, or stories relevant to your presentation to captivate your audience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare for questions about how your research theory relates to practice and vice versa. Practice answering questions, manage your presentation time effectively, and remember that practice makes perfect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customize your questions for each institution to demonstrate that you’ve done your research. Familiarize yourself with the faculty’s work and connect your research to their contributions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;After-the-Interviews-Making-the-Right-Choice&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#After-the-Interviews-Making-the-Right-Choice&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;After the Interviews: Making the Right Choice&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;After the Interviews: Making the Right Choice&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After all the interviews, when you’re faced with multiple offers, consider the following factors to make an informed decision:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Know Your Goals&lt;/strong&gt;: Define what you want from your career. Is it the best business school, a strong IS department, productive faculty, or opportunities for collaboration outside IS?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Salary and Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;: Consider the financial aspects of the offers, including salary, benefits, and any additional perks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Culture, Geography, and Personal Factors&lt;/strong&gt;: Reflect on the institution’s culture, location, and any opportunities it may offer for your spouse or family.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Teaching and Service Load&lt;/strong&gt;: Assess the teaching and service expectations, as well as any requirements for assistant or tenure-track professors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tenure Criteria&lt;/strong&gt;: Understand the specific criteria and expectations for earning tenure at each institution. This includes research productivity, teaching performance, and any service obligations. Ensure they align with your career goals and capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;Summary&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Summary&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Summary&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Summary&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, maximizing your research potential and ensuring your happiness are keys to success in securing a tenure-track position. It’s a competitive journey, but with careful preparation, thoughtful presentation, and consideration of your personal and professional goals, you can increase your chances of landing your dream job in academia. Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a style=&#34;background-color:black;color:white;text-decoration:none;padding:4px 6px;font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &amp;quot;San Francisco&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Ubuntu, Roboto, Noto, &amp;quot;Segoe UI&amp;quot;, Arial, sans-serif;font-size:12px;font-weight:bold;line-height:1.2;display:inline-block;border-radius:3px&#34; href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/@mkvandergriff?utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=photographer-credit&amp;amp;utm_content=creditBadge&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; title=&#34;Download free do whatever you want high-resolution photos from Maranda Vandergriff&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;&lt;svg xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; style=&#34;height:12px;width:auto;position:relative;vertical-align:middle;top:-2px;fill:white&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 32 32&#34;&gt;&lt;title&gt;unsplash-logo&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M10 9V0h12v9H10zm12 5h10v18H0V14h10v9h12v-9z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;thumbnail by Maranda Vandergriff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <guid isPermalink="true">https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2019/09/01/Syllabus-Notes-for-JSOM-Ph-D-Math-Refresher/</guid>
            <title>Syllabus and Notes for JSOM Ph.D. Math Refresher</title>
            <link>https://blog.yihong-liu.com/2019/09/01/Syllabus-Notes-for-JSOM-Ph-D-Math-Refresher/</link>
            <category>JSOM</category>
            <category>Ph.D.</category>
            <category>Notes</category>
            <category>Math</category>
            <category>Preliminary</category>
            <category>Courses</category>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 21:33:51 -0500</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[ &lt;p&gt;This post provides the syllabus and is used to record my notes of JSOM Ph.D Math Refresher 2019.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For clear pdf version notes, you can download it &lt;a href=&#34;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1Un3ydVimJKDA4v532EcJoVSI2nuOc-Jq/view?usp=sharing&#34; title=&#34;Google Drive&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; for you reference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span id=&#34;more&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&#34;Course&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Course&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Course&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Course&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt; Course Title: &lt;strong&gt;Math Refresher&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Term: &lt;strong&gt;August 2019&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Naveen Jindal School of Management, The University of Texas at Dallas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Version: June 11, 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Course-Meeting-Time-Location&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Course-Meeting-Time-Location&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Course Meeting Time &amp;amp; Location&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Course Meeting Time &amp;amp; Location&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt; Dates: August 5, 2018 to August 17, 2019&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Location: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.utdallas.edu/locator/JSOM_2%23!/JSOM_2.801&#34;&gt;JSOM 2.801&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Contact-Information&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Contact-Information&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Contact Information&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Contact Information&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt; Instructor: Dr. Kyle Hyndman&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:KyleB.Hyndman@utdallas.edu&#34;&gt;KyleB.Hyndman@utdallas.edu&lt;/a&gt; Office: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.utdallas.edu/locator/JSOM_3%23!/JSOM_3.614&#34;&gt;JSOM 3.614&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Instructor: Dr. Milind Dawande&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:milind@utdallas.edu&#34;&gt;milind@utdallas.edu&lt;/a&gt; Office: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.utdallas.edu/locator/JSOM_3%23!/JSOM_3.405&#34;&gt;JSOM 3.405&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Course-Description&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Course-Description&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Course Description&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Course Description&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt; This refresher course provides a refresher&amp;#x2F;introduction to the various mathematical tools that will be used in the core classes of the Ph.D. program (Management Science) at the Naveen Jindal School of Management. Topics include set theory, open and closed sets, sequences and limits, compactness, properties of functions (continuity, differentiability, (quasi-)concavity, metric spaces, linear algebra, etc. Emphasis will be placed on developing and using formal mathematical reasoning to prove results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Student-Learning-Objectives&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Student-Learning-Objectives&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Student Learning Objectives&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Student Learning Objectives&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apply formal mathematical reasoning to write logically consistent proofs of important mathematical results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refresh mathematical skills that will be used in MECO 6345 (Advanced Managerial Economics) and OPRE 7353 (Optimization) and throughout the Ph.D.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Textbook-and-Materials&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Textbook-and-Materials&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Textbook and Materials&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Textbook and Materials&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt; There is no textbook for the refresher but we can provide some recommendations, particularly for those for which the content is new.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, Efe A., &lt;em&gt;Real Analysis with Economic Applications&lt;/em&gt;, Princeton University Press.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simon, Carl P. and Lawrence Blume, &lt;em&gt;Mathematics for Economists&lt;/em&gt;, Norton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strichartz, Robert S., &lt;em&gt;The Way of Analysis&lt;/em&gt;, Jones and Bartlett.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt; For a much less advanced treatment, but one which should provide at least cursory coverage of all material, the following may be useful:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;4&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hoy, Michael, John Livernois, Chris McKenna, Ray Rees and Thanasis Stengos, &lt;em&gt;Mathematics for Economics&lt;/em&gt;, Second Edition, MIT Press.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt; There may be more recent editions of each of these books. The exact edition you get is not important, nor is it required that you get any of these books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Tentative-Schedule&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Tentative-Schedule&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Tentative Schedule&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Tentative Schedule&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Meeting&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Date&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Instructor&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Topic&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 05 (M&amp;#x2F;A)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Daw&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Intro. to Mathematical Reasoning, Set Theory, Sequences&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 06 (A, 2:30PM)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Daw&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Problem Solving Session&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 07 (A)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Daw&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Convex Sets&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 08 (M&amp;#x2F;A)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Hyn&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Functions and Their Properties&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 9 (A)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Hyn&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Problem Solving Session&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 10 (M&amp;#x2F;A)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Hyn&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;More on Functions; Metric Spaces and Compactness&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 12 (A)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Hyn&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Problem Solving Session&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;8a&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 13 (M)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Daw&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Problem Solving Session&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;8b&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 13 (A)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Hyn&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Advanced Topics (Correspondences, Fixed Points)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;9&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 14 (M&amp;#x2F;A)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Daw&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Matrices, Vector Spaces, Linear Algebra&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;10&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Aug 17 (A)&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Hyn&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Exam&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt; Notes: 1. “M” refers to a &lt;strong&gt;morning&lt;/strong&gt; session, while “A” refers to an &lt;strong&gt;afternoon&lt;/strong&gt; session. 2. There will be no classes on August 15 or 16, 2019 as there are mandatory PhD program and TA&amp;#x2F;RA orientations for those days.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Course-Structure&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Course-Structure&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Course Structure&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Course Structure&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt; Days with both a morning and afternoon session will primarily consist of more traditional lectures where topics are introduced and formal results are proven. Students are encouraged to participate fully in these sessions with questions as well as contributions for proving results. At the end of each full day, students will be given questions which will be discussed in the following afternoon session. Students should make a good faith effort to answer as many of the questions as possible &lt;strong&gt;before&lt;/strong&gt; the problem solving session. During the problem solving session, &lt;strong&gt;all&lt;/strong&gt; students should be prepared to offer solutions, advice and encouragement regarding the problems being discussed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;Student-Deliverables&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#Student-Deliverables&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34;Student Deliverables&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Student Deliverables&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h1 id=&#34;In-the-last-session-there-will-be-a-short-test-that-students-must-complete-This-results-of-this-test-will-be-passed-along-to-the-respective-Ph-D-Coordinators-for-each-area-Furthermore-we-stress-that-material-from-the-bootcamp-may-return-on-the-preliminary-exam-that-JSOM-students-take-at-the-end-of-the-first-year-Lecture-Notes&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#In-the-last-session-there-will-be-a-short-test-that-students-must-complete-This-results-of-this-test-will-be-passed-along-to-the-respective-Ph-D-Coordinators-for-each-area-Furthermore-we-stress-that-material-from-the-bootcamp-may-return-on-the-preliminary-exam-that-JSOM-students-take-at-the-end-of-the-first-year-Lecture-Notes&#34; class=&#34;headerlink&#34; title=&#34; In the last session, there will be a short test that students must complete. This results of this test will be passed along to the respective Ph.D. Coordinators for each area. Furthermore, we stress that material from the bootcamp may return on the preliminary exam that JSOM students take at the end of the first year.Lecture Notes&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; In the last session, there will be a short test that students must complete. This results of this test will be passed along to the respective Ph.D. Coordinators for each area. Furthermore, we stress that material from the bootcamp may return on the preliminary exam that JSOM students take at the end of the first year.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Lecture Notes&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;justified-gallery&#34; align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/xTb6sJNX/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-001.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 1&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/fySfgpLG/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-002.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 2&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/htWpNDVp/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-003.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 3&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/BnTM0rgs/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-004.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 4&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/DZMc6n2Q/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-005.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 5&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/QMjSxf47/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-006.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 6&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/ZRRc6ChK/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-007.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 7&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/vmXh15kN/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-008.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 8&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/6Tsfsc4y/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-009.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 9&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/kMVrm5tm/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-010.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 10&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/3rzsJHgD/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-011.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 11&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/NfTWKP4C/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-012.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 12&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/7ZndVGjg/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-013.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 13&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/3xTzmCf8/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-014.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 14&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/KY9VXXGj/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-015.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 15&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/vm8jS8dC/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-016.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 16&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/W3hyT9zn/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-017.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 17&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/LXwbXzZM/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-018.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 18&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/D0GYb8q4/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-019.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 19&#34;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.postimg.cc/tRnccmLR/Notes-for-Ph-D-Preliminary-Math-Refresher-2019-2-page-020.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Page 20&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a style=&#34;background-color:black;color:white;text-decoration:none;padding:4px 6px;font-family:-apple-system, BlinkMacSystemFont, &amp;quot;San Francisco&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Helvetica Neue&amp;quot;, Helvetica, Ubuntu, Roboto, Noto, &amp;quot;Segoe UI&amp;quot;, Arial, sans-serif;font-size:12px;font-weight:bold;line-height:1.2;display:inline-block;border-radius:3px&#34; href=&#34;https://unsplash.com/@nate_dumlao?utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=photographer-credit&amp;amp;utm_content=creditBadge&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener noreferrer&#34; title=&#34;Download free do whatever you want high-resolution photos from Nathan Dumlao&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;&lt;svg xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; style=&#34;height:12px;width:auto;position:relative;vertical-align:middle;top:-2px;fill:white&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 32 32&#34;&gt;&lt;title&gt;unsplash-logo&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d=&#34;M10 9V0h12v9H10zm12 5h10v18H0V14h10v9h12v-9z&#34;&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:inline-block;padding:2px 3px&#34;&gt;thumbnail by Nathan Dumlao&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 ]]></description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
